theirishtripleking: My boys hotzzz lets goo
efiggs: Whaddupppp
AppleGrape: CAn MuZero make me money in online hold em
darthbearjew666: Sup sensei?!
cleverz0id: hey
microx0ft: wussup geo
phennessey: NOTICE ME SEMPAI
lanop24: Wohaaaa first time watching live
ogrockefeller: Father!
jnnx74: Can’t stand Alienware and these commercials
mashafique: Hey George
ogrockefeller: Would you join the dark side?
cleverz0id: what is MuZero?
aiex42: Yo bro
darthbearjew666: Sup sensei
mattdougherty22: good to see you
jnnx74: Name it Falken
midnightcookies: developer aint shit lol
mashafique: Will I be noticed
sajugabru: which hoodie is it
lanop24: George big fan
mattdougherty22: when can we learn more about church?
jnnx74: Wouldn’t you prefer a nice game of chess?
bodiddley_33: would you work for U.S. defense?
efiggs: If god is good then why does he allow suffering to exist
th3_maj0r: yoyo
Penguino138: Lets goooo!
microx0ft: how about a game of Go
Penguino138: The number of people that thought you streamed for 19 hours is crazy
efiggs: If god is good then why does he allow suffering to exist
sajugabru: two players
pwnbase: non continuous
braininavatt: George! I thought you've gotten arrested! Kappa
uglykoopa: no
Penguino138: Is it cause we can map out all the tic tac toe moves easily?
microx0ft: bc there is a limited moves
uknyted: Wargames rings a bell.
cutza: tic tac toe but 4x4?
jnnx74: Just don’t play “Global ThermoNuclear War”
braininavatt: PogChamp today's gonna be a productive day VoHiYo
bodiddley_33: George, take LSD
Penguino138: Get MuZero to play Plague Inc
bodiddley_33: have you?
qlutoo: love that movie
lanop24: Hey George what was app called you used for paper search
realvdeal: realvdeal subscribed at Tier 1.
phennessey: Can it win at rock paper scissors
JBNunn: if password == "joshua"
calcmath: -100 reward for illegal move
phennessey: hunter2
InfiniteReddit: hello
bodiddley_33: LSD is a PED
bodiddley_33: performance enhancing drug
dunstableramsay: did you cure coronovirus yet?
Penguino138: @bodiddley_33 stay on topic, we don't talk about drugs unless george says so
braininavatt: dont leave your selfs at home
tallestmollusk: so late stream
hsydf92: tell about corona
ionelaipatioaei: how was the protest?
Emma_Cakes: Hihi <3
majorawpsome: 3 in a row?
lanop24: Anyone know the app he used to search for white papers in 19hour stream
synthetic11000: @lanop24 https://www.zotero.org/
lanop24: Thanks
tallestmollusk: Just do cases: col, row, two diagonals
factor0n: i did look at the gethub for the corona that was amazing shit there
JBNunn: what if you reshape to 9, then look for 3
Mariosavitch: hello mr hotz
realvdeal: :)
coversine: you did import numpy
JBNunn: we test in prod
braininavatt: indentation
TheSkapegoat: Hey chat, how we doing today?
darthbearjew666: If squares are same in 3 in a row?
grenaderaven: wth is that ide
Mariosavitch: tests after implementation. typical hacker
Penguino138: @TheSkapegoat Hopefully chat is good today, a few comments about drugs and corona but we'll get them to stop
dantusqq: i made my car drive itself with arduino hire me.
jomkingal: Pleasant evening george and everyone
realvdeal: Thoughts on coding bootcamps vs college?
goldama: goldama subscribed at Tier 1.
Penguino138: welcome @goldama
bodiddley_33: college is if you have $ and want the college experience
braininavatt: SwiftRage
bodiddley_33: nothing matters besides if u know ur shit or not
TheSkapegoat: Do both @realvdeal start with boot camp to save money
j0ca1995: @georgehotz do you know a lot of html and css?
Mariosavitch: np.shape :P
jomkingal: I went to college and got a degree in computer science, but i still had to learn on the spot on my first job
realvdeal: That's what I was thinking
TheSkapegoat: @jomkingal IT always changes constantly
jomkingal: I think college is a waste of money, you just need dedication
Mariosavitch: we won :)
TheSkapegoat: Its part of what's interesting
jomkingal: @theskapegoat yeah that too
Penguino138: Freaking called it. Told you guys to stay on topic
lexxy23: Tic Tac Toe > Education
simmy7: hi George :D
Penguino138: Unless geo specifies, stay on topic
LightChain09: LightChain09 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
TheSkapegoat: Sorry Geohot lol, my mans had an innocent question
picklesareok: aww thanks george
realvdeal: Sorry guys lmao
Mariosavitch: zips lips.
bscolaro: Kappa
Lost_x_Echo: Ly bb.
theirishtripleking: ooofftta
rshelat97: kapp
LightChain09: Wait twitch prime people cant write in sub only?
xeeton: @georgehotz you watch alphago yet?
Penguino138: @bodiddley_33 we don't talk about drugs
Newlax: freeedom
Newlax: usa usa
picklesareok: yes
Keboburrito: Keboburrito subscribed at Tier 1.
picklesareok: more fun than winning
simmy7: yes
Lost_x_Echo: Do it.
TheSkapegoat: Was the alphago paper enjoyable to read/learn @georgehotz ?
braininavatt: HYYYYYYYYYPE
Penguino138: @bodiddley_33 If you talk about drugs, you're going to ruin it for everyone. I'm trying to help you, or you'll get banned
zahakka: zahakka subscribed with Twitch Prime.
prez7: MrDestructoid
picklesareok: just go listen to some hamilton morris if thats what you wanna talk about
Penguino138: @th3_maj0r please keep an eye on @bodiddley_33
simmy7: cya
picklesareok: f
braininavatt: LUL
Penguino138: peace
bscolaro: later LUL
th3_maj0r: late
lord_alpaca_666: wham bam
lord_alpaca_666: ban
samwilliamson7: What’s good
Penguino138: @th3_maj0r all good im keeping an eye on the chat for off-topic'ers
Killedacow: rip
theirishtripleking: Drop that hammer
austin__be__saucin: we'll you ever be going back to the bioinformatics stuff?
austin__be__saucin: willa*
MoTeMiB: j
mrhdr: NaM
simmy7: george i was just rewatching twitch chess stuff
neuromancer2: neuromancer2 subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 4 months!
Penguino138: HYPE Ttrain
picklesareok: hey george, is this based on the J. Schrittwieser et al paper?
MoTeMiB: Have you ever thought working at apple ?
grekler3: why would he work for someone else LUL
Penguino138: @picklesareok This paper
Penguino138: https://arxiv.org/pdf/1911.08265.pdf
TheSkapegoat: @austin__be__saucin Geohot never stops doing something, he just changes focuses for a mean time
picklesareok: gracias
mindandmoney: mindandmoney subscribed at Tier 1.
cars1n: Hey geo, can the comma ai driving ai play tic tac to
picklesareok: based arxiv
lord_alpaca_666: i would probably say that muzero would be weaker than a bot that just reads every possible move, because tic tac toe is a solved game
calcmath: Give illegal move -100 reward and let the game continue
0xCheckM8: heeeeey geo!
austin__be__saucin: @TheSkapegoat i see
0xCheckM8: sup sup sup?
Mariosavitch: gotta love low quality code
bloopsterr: chat, do you know what colour scheme he uses in iterm?
synthetic11000: George is a 10xer and I'm barely an x-er
badpartyhouse: yeeee
lord_alpaca_666: i am a 1/10xer
Penguino138: Is TicTacToe so simple that all the strats are already figured out, or could an AI still find a new strategy?
simmy7: @bloopsterr should be in his github (config)
badpartyhouse: Finally
bloopsterr: @simmy7 couldnt see it
lord_alpaca_666: can muzero play real-time games?
badpartyhouse: Lets go
Mariosavitch: did it win
badpartyhouse: more machine learning
badpartyhouse: keep it up guys
cars1n: @penguino138 there is like 30 combos for a game of tic tac toe. All possible strats/moves are already found out
0xCheckM8: bro, i have a question.. how do you record your streams and then put them on youtube in high quality? do you have an external hardware or you do all of that on your mac?
Mariosavitch: lol
JamesHarrys: danLurk
youngsachi: LUL
Mariosavitch: im good at learning how to lose.
goldama: Wait, is this a monte carlo method for tic tac toe ?
Penguino138: @cars1n How complex does a game have to be for there to be a seemingly unlimited number of combinations (like GO)?
mabtwitch15: Hey Man!
badpartyhouse: SeemsGood SeemsGood SeemsGood
wingsofcorn: what is the code on the left?
kaksoispistedeh: if it learns to lose, just invert the reward function 5Head
georgehotz: https://github.com/geohot/ai-notebooks
cars1n: @penguino138 idk but its a game with max of 9 moves...
0xCheckM8: please answer my question
Mariosavitch: what kind of coffee do you like mr hotz
badpartyhouse: we can have that drug all day
Penguino138: black espresso blend french press is my fav
picklesareok: but with >300000 possible states
picklesareok: kind of unassuming
badpartyhouse: give me another cup
Penguino138: For those wanting this pseudocode: https://arxiv.org/src/1911.08265v1/anc/pseudocode.py
Mariosavitch: if it works for lunar lander.. worlds first?
toront0saur: hello george
badpartyhouse: that was a really long stream wow
adnp_: Can somebody quickly tell what is he doing tonight?
mabtwitch15: Try out hackerRank again
brofessorbob: coding tictactoe bro
Penguino138: @cod4_lightning He doesn't reupload them. Someone else on a YT channel called Comma AI Archive does. He has a blue yeti mic
xeeton: @adnp_ making muzero play tictactoe
grekler3: anyone else feel like you dont learn anything untill you put it on a paper or a note ? like watching youtube tutorial and only following without noting
Penguino138: @cod4_lightning And he streams with OBS!
cars1n: Isnt he making a machine learning thing that can be easily translated to playing different games
goldama: yes @grekler3 always best to code and do it yourself for learning
picklesareok: @grekler3 you gotta learn by actually doing! you can read until your blue in the face
0xCheckM8: @penguino138 I mean how does he record them and store them?
godlessmonkey: What are we doing?
Penguino138: @cod4_lightning Subscribers can access VOD and download them using some third party app I'm guessing
th3_maj0r: Did u put this code on github?
cars1n: Arent the youtube vids just the ripped twitch vods
th3_maj0r: yes
motivatedpeasant: Do it
deva73: yes
cars1n: You seriously need to make a Rock Paper Scissors ai
neuromancer2: The only winning move is not to play
Penguino138: @th3_maj0r github for this stream: https://github.com/geohot/ai-notebooks
danteernande: Hello George
motivatedpeasant: Has Eric Weinstein hit you up to go on his podcast?
grekler3: @picklesareok yeah but i guess first read and note, then practice, i cant just practice and follow along, without noting
0xCheckM8: cod4_lightning subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 3 months! Twitch told me to tell you that i've been subscribed for 3 months!
yurifonseca: yurifonseca subscribed with Twitch Prime.
lolfulloftrolls: geohot, do you still rap?
sammy_the_slayer: <3
th3_maj0r: @Penguino138 ty
grekler3: PogChamp
Penguino138: He released a song a few weeks ago
zenkai_oogway: PogChamp
Mariosavitch: stick to programming
sammy_the_slayer: PogChamp
cars1n: George do you have any interest in neuroscience and technological applications for it? Like making a 1 to 1 brain simulation or a computer that functions similarly to the brain
mabtwitch15: Try out hackerRank again
lolfulloftrolls: riivGasm
zenkai_oogway: he s p i t t i n
Twistedbane: fire
codezillla: swaggg
Penguino138: Bruh im totally gonna take this rap and stick a beat on it
TheKoreanZombi: That hot fire though!
codezillla: SeemsGood
vrv_exe: Ohhh damn
lolfulloftrolls: itwasmNeat
realvdeal: Bruh
mohamed_adel96: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
lolfulloftrolls: nice
travbicklee: WutFace
saucyjin: not half bad
codezillla: that was legendary
Penguino138: I'm waiting for the VOD then it'll be ready
mabtwitch15: Try out hackerRank again
mweldo: barsbarsbarsbars
guy_ross: CurseLit CurseLit CurseLit
lolfulloftrolls: I remember your Sony lawsuit rap
codezillla: barss
travbicklee: cbrahFor cbrahThe cbrahBoys
picklesareok: boy did i pick the wrong time for a bathroom breakk
IMTotes: we back to muzero?
IMTotes: no lander?
Penguino138: dotsHappy
Twistedbane: Kreygasm
cars1n: stompTrash
0xCheckM8: sup?
l1ght5p33d: yeeeaaaaa
l1ght5p33d: why
l1ght5p33d: is muzero minimax with extra layers?
guccibruf: did he manage to balance the cartpole, or is this still trying to get the muzero to work
Mdog1224: How do I get started with ml
l1ght5p33d: muzero was optimized for cartpole pretty much
Penguino138: yeah it struggled a bit more with the lander
l1ght5p33d: just want the whole lookup table with amax every time... must try to be more subtle
jsnake794: ayy
SamuelTheBoi: ayy
l1ght5p33d: if already have child
l1ght5p33d: make tree 3x as large
Mariosavitch: -float("inf") Pog
l1ght5p33d: i thought he uses keras isn't every function already written
Penguino138: honk
Keboburrito: time to write tests?
LiveCustoms: George what are you're thoughts on smart drugs?
Suspecthum: How do you deal with nihilism?
Mariosavitch: what are these questions
coversine: exponential algorithms are fun
TheKoreanZombi: 20k
l1ght5p33d: so fast we have it so easy these days
SHAVEYY_: 1
Mariosavitch: 3^9
TheKoreanZombi: 3^9
LiveCustoms: 3; tick, tack and toe
theislenotdev: You can rotate and mirror the field so you can reduce a shitton @georgehotz
l1ght5p33d: is there linting for jupyter?
AseriOCE: @georgehotz have you ever tried stuff with computational physics or physics engines?
Mariosavitch: 1.. we win
calcmath: make a tupleise decoratoer
Mariosavitch: it beat itself. so does that mean its smarter than itself
guccibruf: i can hear it
Penguino138: Mic very sensitive :')
ak0ya_: wiki says 765 positions
num_air: the mic is too good
ak0ya_: and 26830 possible games
aiex42: not 3^9
LiveCustoms: Hell yeah
brofessorbob: Jam out
Mariosavitch: ban him
num_air: hell yeaahhh bro
Penguino138: how copyrighted? underground or taylor swift?
theislenotdev: you can mirror and rotate
TheKoreanZombi: Copyrighted music is best music
Keboburrito: feelin copyrighted beats
AseriOCE: @georgehotz if you don't care about the vods go hard af
ak0ya_: many symmetries
SHAVEYY_: yes PogChamp
LiveCustoms: Play some One Direction pls
LiveCustoms: KappaPride
Iluvmf: Did you make lunarlander work?
Iluvmf: Wasnt there till the end last time
TheKoreanZombi: @Iluvmf No
l1ght5p33d: why is ht representation
Jehhred: *paying attention*
happypuppppy: ok i'm listening :)
Shifunei: am i the only one who watches while pretending that I know what's going on 4Head
num_air: you are not the only one bro
mindandmoney: hahahah im right there with you
pzuko7: dont worry i just started to learn coding lol
l1ght5p33d: ALWAYS SHAPEEE
xgutsgoesberserk: is he making tic tac toe ai
Mariosavitch: lol
TheKoreanZombi: Class dismissed
l1ght5p33d: beautifully
calcmath: no more neural network issues
opus_000: ai Shakespeare
ak0ya_: what about other searches?
ak0ya_: do they work?
ak0ya_: like naive
DeeboMC: Tic tac toe huh? Major shift
guinness84: seem 6 month olds smarter than ur search bro
kayoeyumisaolegais: !uptime
DeeboMC: Is lunar lander over? Like covid over.. or is this just a break
LiveCustoms: wut
l1ght5p33d: don't know
IMTotes: mmm yes ofc
Mariosavitch: LUL
calcmath: always 0 lol
IMTotes: i understand
TheKoreanZombi: 0 is great action
l1ght5p33d: lel
goldama: lmao action 0 is the best
Iluvmf: lol
badpartyhouse: BibleThump
LiveCustoms: dude im a CPA don't ask me I only know how to do tax returns
xeeton: I'm disappointed in every one of you
th3_maj0r: always blue always blue
Iluvmf: Maybe lunarlander will work now
residentsleeperrrrrrrrr: this guy actually think hes getting somewhere?
shaselton: tests ftw!
linux_____: I just tuned in cant be blamed
l1ght5p33d: i fixed follower its just hard when its blurry on twitch
Mariosavitch: because your big head is in the way
DeeboMC: @iluvmf Does it apply?
me98h: is jupyter better than google colab ?
calcmath: if no zoom code, then no correct your code
Iluvmf: @DeeboMC Was he using this function? cant remember
DeeboMC: Yea that’s what I’m unsure of as well
thecoder15: woot owot
TheKoreanZombi: You didn't say it was code review. You said "pay attention and you will learn something"
aiex42: not 3^9 bc many infeasible & equivalent game states
Iluvmf: @I know he was using naive_search at some point
thecoder15: anyone here know much about the uber layoff ?
l1ght5p33d: do uber drivers have jobs?
TheKoreanZombi: Brilliant!
Mariosavitch: it foookin knows
goldama: gg
Penguino138: Search them certainy trees
DeeboMC: They did for awhile.. I only know via news. I live in a town too small for ride-sharing companies
lanop24: I can't beleive I am watching live.
TheKoreanZombi: AlphaNegativeOne
guinness84: congrats
LiveCustoms: How are your STONKS doing Georgio?
DeeboMC: Believe it lmao
ilovesaikat: should i buy tesla
borang: follow for that notification
l1ght5p33d: seems legit
Mariosavitch: didnt have enough variations?
thecoder15: did you quit the bio stuff ?
calcmath: block a win
Mariosavitch: to prevent a win
l1ght5p33d: more options to win
DeeboMC: Yeah @thecoder15
s___t___r___i___x: !muzero
ffntdt: did anyone here was invited by google foobar?
Mariosavitch: so its defensive at first.. interesting
ffntdt: was8
ak0ya_: @thecoder15 bio is over
TheKoreanZombi: @thecoder15 Yeah, bio stuff too easy. Moved to the ancient game of tic-tac-toe
thecoder15: what we working on now @DeeboMC
WistfulFella: It's just sad that I come in, and I don't understand a thing :(
l1ght5p33d: lets do snek
thecoder15: what is MUZero
DeeboMC: Machine learning library
Penguino138: @thecoder15 MuZero, which is a complex algorithmic AI that does basically advanced MiniMax
Vackin: muzero cousin actionzero
TheKoreanZombi: What is google?
AlexTogo_: He use chromium browser ?
DeeboMC: Potential ai applications not quite an ai
lordFOE: thoughts on brave browser
thecoder15: is it a play on googles one they just released @Penguino138
lordFOE: 😎
xeeton: is that affected by the discount?
Penguino138: @thecoder15 Idk much of the history of it just know about the algo sorry :/
thecoder15: Oh its a deep mind thing
Mariosavitch: lots of games are symetrical
thecoder15: nvm
GoTo3: @georgehotz what do you think of the latest AutoPilot feature?
DeeboMC: Lol np, I’m actually noob myself most ppl in here know more than me I’d assume
singularitytoatea: Pretty fucking sick
instagrab: wholly shit, the legend is on twitch stream. This is some exciting stuff.
Vackin: can we win multidimensional tic tac toe
Mariosavitch: center square
thecoder15: @georgehotz my friend and i worked on a ml library for robotics do you think the market needs a ML system that does everything on the GPU instead of just sending matrix operations off for the GPU to perform?
calcmath: imshow the value function
Mariosavitch: lol
Klingenwetzer: HEYYY DAD!
Mariosavitch: worst possible move
Mariosavitch: i dont think it knows that the player state is switching?
DeeboMC: I’d like to hear his answer to that lol
Mariosavitch: could be wrong
Klingenwetzer: Tmux FeelsGoodMan
RSPwner_: how does one learn about the control theory used in openpilot? ive been working an acc system and want to learn more
WistfulFella: Am I the only one here that does not know what's all of this?
DeeboMC: Highly unlike
DeeboMC: Unlikely
0xCheckM8: @WistfulFella You're not alone my brother
Klingenwetzer: LUL
asvp_sui: Im with you @wistfulfella
ak0ya_: yes
Mariosavitch: yes
TheKoreanZombi: Yes
goldama: yes
georgehotz: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Minimax
l1ght5p33d: tree for games
xeeton: yes
SHAVEYY_: no I only know VIM
RSPwner_: just joined man, no harm sorry
DeeboMC: Yea
tsAllySparkles: oh i wrote a minmax function for tic tac toe
tsAllySparkles: for csci 1300
tsAllySparkles: full tree search
badpartyhouse: Its like creating a chat bot
l1ght5p33d: count paths to win and loss for each state
Klingenwetzer: yes
badpartyhouse: hhhmmmm thats a good way to think about it
tsAllySparkles: recursion depth
Jehhred: This is some next level Nash Equilibrium
DeeboMC: Gettin him to talk “remedially” .. consider yourself lucky
instagrab: Have you ever considered teaching?
Klingenwetzer: complexity
Penguino138: @instagrab He is teaching
badpartyhouse: Make a master class! I will buy it
DeeboMC: Absolutely not @instagrab smart ppl general brisk at the idea of reaching *professionally*
l1ght5p33d: things are good from history
DeeboMC: Teaching*
l1ght5p33d: like bishop attacking queen state
picklesareok: you just calculate that liklihhood with the random unrooling right?
picklesareok: forgetting what we did in class
l1ght5p33d: *defended
BlueSeamoose: Do you play console games in your free time?
instagrab: lol...okay
Bootstraps: hi george
thecoder15: @georgehotz my friend and i worked on a ml library for robotics ML system that does everything on the GPU instead of just sending matrix operations off for the GPU to perform? Do you think this is something that is missing in the toolset we have today
jasondesante: tic tac toe can be brute forced on a few sheets of paper tho
Penguino138: For those of you who want to follow along with the pseudocode: https://arxiv.org/src/1911.08265v1/anc/pseudocode.py
dontbeameme: I wish George would expose all these “Pro” gamers for their cheating
DeeboMC: @penguino138 thanks bruv
Mariosavitch: we are talking about muzero and minimax why are you guys bringing up that stuff
dontbeameme: @mariosavitch Good point
browniongg: chill dudes
goldama: that's not the point jason, mcts is necessary for Go or Chess where trees are impossible to fully recurse
instagrab: @dontbeameme or you can just get at the game lol
Mariosavitch: you cant have 10 observations on a blank slate when the move is always for player 1 to move?
Penguino138: How does a larger tree recursion algorithm for say GO decide how deep to check?
dontbeameme: @instagrab Dude, don’t be a sheep
l1ght5p33d: why are there ten
nsielicki: good evening ya'll
dontbeameme: Good evening
instagrab: @dontbeameme maybe stop complaining on something that is completely irrelevant lol
DeeboMC: @goldama are they *truly* impossible in theory? I think not. At least in chess I know for sure that the number of all possible rules-allowed permutations has been calculated.. so I’d presume it’s only “impossible” in practically.. currently
dontbeameme: @instagrab True
spitzerkid: [1, 0, 1, 0, 0,-1, 1, -1, 0]
DeeboMC: Board-state permutations
Ham3113: after this if you wanted to try another turn based game with muzero then connect foyr which has a slightly higher branching factor of <7. pretty interesting but simple game to look at if you were ever interested.
instagrab: Does this have a GUI like Deep mind, where it controls the game input? Maybe I am blowing this out of proportion lol
Ham3113: yeah lol for sure
Biniano7: I know this is a random question but have you Abu experience with csgo cheats and how VALVE detects cheats?
Ham3113: no rush of course im just saying that was my AI progression. i went from tic tac toe to connect four to chess
goldama: I guess it is only impossible practically yes, it would be physically possible yes
Mariosavitch: is it possible you can go in the to right so we can see whats behind your head?
DeeboMC: 👍🏽
myaocat: LULW
mashafique: LUL
Penguino138: Santiago_LHC missing to lay down the mod hammer
browniongg: KEK
dontbeameme: LULW
DeeboMC: @penguino138 My thoughts exactly
l1ght5p33d: wtf is env.dynamics
nsielicki: did george ever report whether lunar lander was fixed but just throwing more iterations at it?
nsielicki: is this the first stream since sunday?
DeeboMC: If he did I missed it
killa1157: whats up
DeeboMC: Yes I believe it is
killa1157: what you doing today?
calcmath: been since start of this stream, he hasnt mentioned lunar lander at all
aiex42: [1, 0, 1, -1, 1, -1, 0, 0, 0] is not a very good x player
browniongg: yep
dontbeameme: !PC
rafaelbco: i feel dumb watching you doing this stuff
instagrab: @rafaelbco I feel you lol
calcmath: what does the max do when there are ties
Klingenwetzer: primeagenLove primeagenLove primeagenLove primeagenLove
myaocat: trees=combinations?
killa1157: im just here to to say hi to the kid that jailbroke the ps
chair_78: is this just vanilla mcts, or are you making predictions with a model? mcts is not that slow
Penguino138: bi-winning
dontbeameme: I hate super strong AI
DeeboMC: Lmao
rokedev: beard looking extra masculine
dontbeameme: I like to have a chance to win in games
nsielicki: 064 is winning? 012
TheKoreanZombi: ^
nsielicki: 012 345 678
nsielicki: agh formatting fucks up
shlver: D:
hAhamza: Nice one George finally off basic programming
browniongg: FeelsBadMan
dontbeameme: @nsielicki 🔥🔥🔥
vxsery: Why was it allowed to play the same spot twice?
calcmath: its allowed, just high negative reard
calcmath: reward*
nsielicki: winning sets are 123 456 789 047 158 269 059 357
qube_si: Why is the mcts even looking at moves which are impossible?
borang: nsielicki you sure?
TheKoreanZombi: 047 is winning?
calcmath: its not allowed to knoe the rules
nsielicki: sorry offbyone
nsielicki: 036 is winning
TheKoreanZombi: Yeah on a few of those
DeeboMC: @calcmath this
Penguino138: Paper for you reference: https://arxiv.org/pdf/1911.08265.pdf
l1ght5p33d: where is the reward
info303: isn't that the whole point behind muzero? that you don't need to explicitly specify legal moves
chair_78: maybe you're making greedy predictions
DeeboMC: *talks about illegal moves* “mfker be snitchin”
l1ght5p33d: lets see the reward funciton
l1ght5p33d: thank god got a screenshot
Mariosavitch: its "dream" heheh
slapusillydawg: you cracked it
slapusillydawg: the ultimate strategy
slapusillydawg: force your opponent to make illegal moves
calcmath: illegal reard cant always be negative, it should flip with user
killa1157: +1
Mariosavitch: its a nightmare
mashafique: motivational george PogChamp
DeeboMC: Adidaw
dontbeameme: George 2020 “only dream of winning”
TheKoreanZombi: Nash Equilibrium of Losing
nsielicki: aww yeah
borang: rockin
TheKoreanZombi: This band is too indie for us to get copyblocked
DeeboMC: I’m mad I’m like 5-7 seconds delayed
Mariosavitch: do you track the state of whose turn it is
killa1157: 1.0 value of reward?
guishade: hello george, is there an "exponential reward" so the training gets more "risky" every iteration if it wins? like in human learning? wdyt?
l1ght5p33d: print( s ) plz
DeeboMC: Its grandma and the node and the node is you
chair_78: it should get less risky after time
ltn_bob: George are you still part of PPP?
Waldoqq: QUARENTINE GEORGE IS BACK <3
DepressedAndBroken: The gift of young love
ghassane20a: hi
monaliso: george, what grape do you prefer on wines
DeeboMC: 🔨
ofaas: anyone put this stream in the background to code to? it motivates me lol
nsielicki: ;_;
aj37z: I LOVE losing
Penguino138: We're gonna win so hard you're gonna be tired of winning dotsKpog
volere: cucks arent losers #normalizecuckolds
DeeboMC: 😂
nsielicki: can you get please rid of the "address of object" printing in that print_tree function
ghassane20a: can we make a 5x5 tic tac toe
Penguino138: Bringing a new meaning to: "Optimise your loss function"
Mariosavitch: that means its obviously not aligned with who is moving
GeneralGauss: reverse psychology
TheKoreanZombi: But does Player 1 love losing like Player 2 does? We will see.
chair_78: 10 bucks says this is off by one error
madebyollin: Waiting for George to spring into Systematic Mode here and crack this case wide open
DeeboMC: In 4 the losing
DeeboMC: @chair_78 Not twice in a row
ghassane20a: there a piping sound in background
Penguino138: @ghassane20a that's a computer fan
ghassane20a: @Penguino138 hmm ok
DeeboMC: why’s this heating ur cpu so much?
kayoeyumisaolegais: hey can someone explain to me HOW sites are invaded? like, how the code or etc go inside the code and fuck with it....
0R4NG3: lol
Penguino138: @kayoeyumisaolegais keep it on topic
DeeboMC: NotLikeThis
RoyalStarKiller: Is MuZero the deepmind AI?
kayoeyumisaolegais: @Penguino138 ....k
DeeboMC: No
RoyalStarKiller: derivative?
DeeboMC: Yeah
RoyalStarKiller: Gotcha
RoyalStarKiller: thx
DeeboMC: Oh my bad
Penguino138: Black Coffee cheers
0xCheckM8: what coffee are you drinking? Hot or cold?
nsielicki: @kayoeyumisaolegais the program has a bunch of inputs into it and sometimes those inputs end up accidentally spilling into the code and then smart people are able to make the program jump to places it wasn't supposed to place or execute things it wasn't meant to execute
eeXecute: cikd
eeXecute: cold judging by ice sound
Klingenwetzer: FeelsBadMan
JdPaulBlart: @georgehotz see if muzero can solve your programming challenge for commaai
Klingenwetzer: too complex FeelsBadMan
RoyalStarKiller: LUL
aj37z: the conclusion of every ML engineer
0xCheckM8: Have you tried death wish coffee?
DeeboMC: @nsielicki succinct LUL
calcmath: it loves move 7
Mariosavitch: can you push your latest
l1ght5p33d: geohot is the ultra leet
gelatram: !uptime
litesam: 2H i think
calcmath: for sake of illegal moves yes
gelatram: he's already put 20ish hours hasn't he
qube_si: The turn seems to be "-1" instead of "1"
kayoeyumisaolegais: @nsielicki like...obstruct the way or the thing tat should be doing?
nsielicki: show game code again
nsielicki: rewards
nsielicki: @kayoeyumisaolegais idk it's complicated go to school
kayoeyumisaolegais: @nsielicki skks good
DeeboMC: @royalstarkiller So muzero is the deepminds derivative of its own ai.. alphazero ➡️ muzero
jmp0ut: ever been dna and brain jacked?
jmp0ut: optogenomics weaponry
jmp0ut: get it
ShredderSherlock: how are there 6 plays already on the first turn
calcmath: rewards not being flipped properly still
jmp0ut: Nonary (base 9, each digit is two ternary digits
jmp0ut: computation
ShredderSherlock: so you're not having it play the game correctly from the start then no?
jmp0ut: nonary fourier transformation
jmp0ut: inverse fast fourier it and banged out
DeeboMC: @kayoeyumisaolegais @nsielicki don’t necessarily have to “go to school” but you do necessarily have to “educate yourself”.. in some manner; many quality options exist outside the brick and mortar offerings
contrambulance: How did u start to learn coding languages???
nsielicki: @DeeboMC for sure
nsielicki: I hated school
calcmath: who doesnt
DeeboMC: Same, for the most part. Although i always loved learning
borang: the learning part of school is great, fk all the other bs
DeeboMC: Exactly
l1ght5p33d: newzero
nsielicki: VoteYea
DeeboMC: Muzero = newzero
RafaLive: can you pipe that through the an:us15 variable
raiikouu: funny because anus ratirlGiggle
calcmath: useful comments in code
Eolios: wht's the tldr of what he working on chat
DeeboMC: Coding something to win tic tac toe
scem: tic tac toe ai too ez u should design in for chess and end up coding for 4 days stright
Eolios: oh ok ty
scem: straight*
DeeboMC: He already did chess awhile back
calcmath: in those partially played games, does root mean what you want it to mean
32bitrobo: You're a cool dude man, kee doing science
DeeboMC: Spelling only matters in code lol
Brun0Lass: Do you use Wampp Sever?
goldama: let it
Mariosavitch: we go first
l1ght5p33d: randint(0,1)
DeeboMC: Speling in oad comints can bee fucd too know efekt
Mariosavitch: non binary
DeeboMC: Coad*
Mariosavitch: its dumb
Mariosavitch: rofl
eeXecute: its special :0
goldama: rip mcts
aj37z: model was an accident
Ham3113: really rekt him huh lol
ArosGeo: LUL
Ham3113: its a win and a loss really
ArosGeo: what happens if you keep going after you iwn?
ArosGeo: win*
l1ght5p33d: 1337 74C 703
Waldoqq: BIG BRAIN 5Head
DeeboMC: What’s that hex memeing?
nsielicki: having watched these streams over the weekend and talking to a buddy and seeing some of his attempts at lunar lander and tictactoe and polecart, and running them on my own machine, that's my guess as to a LOT of why we're getting weird results, needs more compute in general
Jehhred: Muzero has the brain of a kitchen sponge, confirmed
ShredderSherlock: you need to punish it for it to learn
Mariosavitch: does it know that the state ends?
DeeboMC: @nsielicki why, have you and your buddy been getting better results?
l1ght5p33d: "overfit"
badpartyhouse: Can you do modeling learning?
litesam: try finishing the whole game by filling values
calcmath: its oponents is a clone of itself
Mariosavitch: yeah, it doesnt know it lost already
Terminal_Bash: sounds
badpartyhouse: It might just not gotten to that kind of appoinent
nsielicki: @DeeboMC not "better" results, and not in implementing this particular algorithm
Terminal_Bash: sounds like overfitting
nsielicki: but it does converge after 2 hours of running
info303: are you giving it negative reward for losing?
goldama: Does it think positive reward is good for him ?
badpartyhouse: Give it less reward when you go more in a row
leesingods: yesss finally made one
badpartyhouse: so if you got 3 in a row give it a lot of negative reward
calcmath: no reward shaping allowed
DeeboMC: That’s a meta-concept with regard to the rules
badpartyhouse: hwy?
badpartyhouse: is it allowed to make the first move?
aiex42: "Does it understand why it's stupid" LOL
TheDkbay: "Does it understand why it's stupid" Me to myself when I find a dumb bug in mycode
leesingods: George have you seen the movie Tau?
badpartyhouse: maybe it wins if it makes the first move?
nsielicki: they always say, "ok retard" they never ask "are you ok, retard?"
DeeboMC: It only knows 3 in a row; it hasn’t made the connect to blocking the opponent’s potential for 3?
l1ght5p33d: make move heat map
burzum_: what happened to the corona reverse engineering?
nsielicki: i mean in real life tictactoe its an entirely different game if you go first or second because you either learn to defend or attack
l1ght5p33d: we just didn't finish writing it yet
calcmath: go line by line over ur mcts
l1ght5p33d: *you I like saying we from maths books. bad habit
thekalkulator: are you trying to figure out the proof to never losing?
eeXecute: he doesn't want to beat its creator
dongmuya: doesn't it depend on who goes first?
calebsuhy: calebsuhy subscribed with Twitch Prime.
calcmath: shouldnt u just compare to_play eith -1 or 1 to choose sign of value
Mariosavitch: are you suppose to pass in the entire observation, including the player to move? is that suppose to just be the possible move states?
Santiago_LHC: How is chat doing?
DeeboMC: @l1ght5p33d “‘we’ from maths books” 😂 I can tell you math’d a lot in ur life lol
Ham3113: @calcmath whats your relation with george if you dont mind me asking or are you just really knowledgable amd interested in the same stuff as he is
St47ik: @Santiago_LHC going to bed soon SeemsGood u good?
Ham3113: or both
Ham3113: probably both
nsielicki: it's weird to me how you're doing reversed search_path and then taking the front of the list -- so just the first bnode in that loop
Santiago_LHC: Good good
calcmath: the later @Ham3113
Ham3113: ahhh
info303: are you reversing the value based on which player it is?
qazxswedcvfrtgbnhyujm: do you need to multiply by -1 on line 112 depending on parity of distance from root
Ham3113: cool man yoi sound really smart every time i see you chat
Ham3113: very knowledgable in Muzero
l1ght5p33d: kek
calcmath: the sign flipping is supposed to be happening in line 121 @qazxswedcvfrtgbnhyujm
DeeboMC: @ham3113 you’ll find his streams attract a lot of that; just an observation
aiex42: if X starts, there are 91 distinct positions that can be won by X and only 44 distinct positions can be won by O
calcmath: i am not realy that knowledgable in muzero. just learning along with him
l1ght5p33d: it has become self aware with subjective preference for 7 as one of the low primes
qazxswedcvfrtgbnhyujm: i think you need to sign flip both times
qazxswedcvfrtgbnhyujm: one is the sum, the other is the value at a node
Ham3113: @deebomc yeah it makes me motivated to learn more AI stuff cause i really like these kind of projects
DeeboMC: Same 👍🏽
Ham3113: still working on learning neural networks
nsielicki: i find it nothing short of demotivational, this shit is so hard
Tegach_: Wow been watching all your vids, first time seeing ya live! How's it going George
info303: here is the MCTS implementation for alphazero: https://github.com/AppliedDataSciencePartners/DeepReinforcementLearning/blob/master/MCTS.py
DeeboMC: 😂 well that’s the underside of the coin if you choose to flip it
DeeboMC: @nsielicki
calcmath: @qazxswedcvfrtgbnhyujm i think you might be right
inveritatem: georgehotz does streaming on twitch keep you disciplined in spending more time on these topics or would you be doing this regardless of whether you're streaming or not
l1ght5p33d: nice
goldama: so reading the pseudocode, they put node.to_play = to_play when expanding the root, not the inverse as you have. don't know if that matters
nsielicki: that's a very good lead right there
goldama: node.to_play is the history.to_play
727_tf: still doing the muzero stuff?
mellowcider: Defcon this year?
calcmath: flip sign at line 125 as well?
dongmuya: A strange game. The only winning move is not to play. How about a nice game of chess?
St47ik: @727_tf it's in the title 4Head
727_tf: oh shit didnt see
727_tf: i thought he was done after the lunar lander thing the other day
nsielicki: inb4 defcon is cancelled
727_tf: i guess i misheard
JdPaulBlart: lemme play muzero in tic tac toe
DeeboMC: @tegach_ don’t expect a reply to something mundane when he was obviously engrossed in something before you popped in; @inveritatem the latter obviously.. what do u think he did before twitch??? He obviously didn’t start being interested in the subject matter concurrent with the invention of twitch
St47ik: @dongmuya winning by not playing or keeping the high reward of not losing LUL
JdPaulBlart: dude...
JdPaulBlart: calm down jeez
calcmath: @georgehotz flip sign at line 125 as well?
info303: ^
DeeboMC: Just sayin; it’s so annoying im vicariously annoyed for him 😆
nsielicki: i'm off to bed, peace ya'll
St47ik: good night
RSPwner_: what are good acc algorithms? curious
DeeboMC: Peace bro
Unity3g: is mac better for coding?
xProtheanx: !uptime
xProtheanx: !time
onebitbrain: would you like to play a game? muZero -> no!
info303: where is that pseudocode from the paper?
DeeboMC: @tegach_ sorry for being a dick, man. Anyway, welcome to your first live stream
georgehotz: https://arxiv.org/src/1911.08265v2/anc/pseudocode.py
DeeboMC: Nah @georgehotz that was me saying peace to @nsielicki
calcmath: more print stmts needed for debug
ToxicVulpes: @georgehotz have u tried the cicaada3301 puzzles?
l1ght5p33d: my thought exactly
THX1342: line 280 there's a legal_actions f
info303: they do sign flipping based on whose turn it is if I understand it correctly when updating the value_sum
chowzor: I didn't read muzero paper too much, but doesn't the reward come from running the MCTS sims?
Goooshlrific: can you display what your montecarlo tree search function is doing? whats that last argument representing the # of playouts?
l1ght5p33d: @Goooshlrific reward from the print statement
qazxswedcvfrtgbnhyujm: i think their value is always +1 for the winner, but yours is +1 for +1 and -1 for -1
gigafact: Hello everyone. Hello George.
lord_alpaca_666: this is like the ending of "wargames"
chowzor: Yeah I am not sure if this like the minimax
Goooshlrific: negamax vs min max
calcmath: double flipping occurring lol
MrMcaustin1: MrMcaustin1 subscribed at Tier 2. They've subscribed for 3 months! Three months at tier two baby
semihchelik: v
chowzor: Aren't you using the same network for both players?
calcmath: along with value sum store what values are being summed in a list as well?
onebitbrain: i think we want it to output "The only way to win is not to play"
RSPwner_: i see you comma uses ACADO toolbox for MPC algorithms in ACC, have you looked into ForcesPRO?
calcmath: this is what @qazxswedcvfrtgbnhyujm long ago lol
DeeboMC: Negamax - It’s just like, it’s just like, a mini max.. hey, hey... https://youtu.be/FJ3oHpup-pk
RSPwner_: where could i go to learn more about stuff for comma?
Santiago_LHC: The internet
RSPwner_: : )
chowzor: Coool
l1ght5p33d: GG
Ham3113: nice
axlebear: PogChamp
leesingods: ggwp
axlebear: Kappa
k00kieeeez: xqcM
Mariosavitch: not me :)
qazxswedcvfrtgbnhyujm: 10
Goooshlrific: top right
RSPwner_: 3
badpartyhouse: 5
Goooshlrific: then bottom left
Krakatoa77: middle
axlebear: me :)
Ham3113: 0
qazxswedcvfrtgbnhyujm: top right again
badpartyhouse: center
Mariosavitch: 8
leesingods: put it in a place that doesnt make sense to
Goooshlrific: bottom right
onebitbrain: random.choice()
badpartyhouse: bottom left
badpartyhouse: right
Ham3113: 4
goldama: bottom right
badpartyhouse: lol
Goooshlrific: wewin
Mariosavitch: 8!1
chowzor: 99999
sit_d: center
badpartyhouse: center
Krakatoa77: 4
Lourned: middle
Mariosavitch: center
Goooshlrific: we won
prakyath_kantharaju: Do 0 - > 6 -> 9 its a trap and trick test it with that.
727_tf: dumb compooter
badpartyhouse: we win
badpartyhouse: yea
gigafact: lol
Mariosavitch: we tricked it..w e WON
Lourned: easy win Kappa
Mariosavitch: WE WON
phrixus_bro: ez
badpartyhouse: ahaha
Ham3113: lol
727_tf: gg ez
Mariosavitch: We smart
DeeboMC: What is the chat doing rn?
Ham3113: ez win lets go chat
sit_d: lol
Goooshlrific: we won on its first move
Mariosavitch: we smart.
prakyath_kantharaju: Do moves 0 - > 6 -> 9 its a trap and trick test it with that.
badpartyhouse: yea
onebitbrain: galaxy brain
axlebear: EZ Clap
prakyath_kantharaju: Do move 0 - > 6 -> 9 its a trap and trick test it with that.
badpartyhouse: well it is hard to beat if you do it that way
calcmath: test with mumodel
Lourned: 200 IQ game
Santiago_LHC: Hive mind
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: @georgehotz link it to twitchtictactoe
badpartyhouse: you win 80% of the time
zaidoc: we smart we loyal
lord_alpaca_666: can you make it compete with a deterministic bot
lord_alpaca_666: and compare the performance
leesingods: 302 brains better than MuZero
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: BlessRNG @georgehotz link it with twitchtictactoe and deploy ipfs
zaidoc: is this machine learning tic tac toe?
Ham3113: yo gotta go now george and chat. see y'all later. hop the mcts wrecks you in tic tac toe soon lol
Goooshlrific: can you describe your mcts implementation, and when training occurs on the network?
32bitrobo: see ya brother
calcmath: later Ham
chowzor: Next can you teach it to get me a gf?
0xCheckM8: you should drink death wish coffee
Lourned: i think teaching a monkey to play tic tac toe is easier Kappa
Ham3113: peace : )
prakyath_kantharaju: Do 0 - > 6 -> 9 its a trap and trick test it with that.
goldama: on computer second move, 3 is a bad move but it still played it
axlebear: is it legal to put it in a robot and let it loose
luggy_b0i: @zaidoc Yep.
borang: 9 isn't a space broski
info303: it beat you haha
Mariosavitch: give it more simulatiokns
Krakatoa77: 6 is winning move
Goooshlrific: lol
Goooshlrific: it played itself
l1ght5p33d: scipy docs suck
l1ght5p33d: numpy docs suck
l1ght5p33d: only google docs
l1ght5p33d: r good
Lourned: what happened to experts exchange? I remember it was legit back in the days
DeeboMC: [Chat atency test; ping back asap] *ping*
0xCheckM8: ping 8.8.8.8
zaidoc: this is way over my head, one day i will learn...
DeeboMC: Ok cool; not bad
l1ght5p33d: docs that suck include : Apple, php, also entire microsoft
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: @georgehotz train it for a dots game? You get more than 3x3 to play with
Mariosavitch: np nan
l1ght5p33d: Docker has good docs from the name i suppose
jmv_chin: that's a whole lotta code for tic tac toe
0xCheckM8: @georgehotz what to do you say on books like this: https://nostarch.com/seriouspython
Goooshlrific: mAcHiNe LeRn
l1ght5p33d: each move takes exponentially longer
jmv_chin: computer doing the big brain think
ResonatorGames: how about exhaustive search tic tac toe? About 30 lines :P
Mariosavitch: a policy of losing
qazxswedcvfrtgbnhyujm: how about big data hopscotch next
l1ght5p33d: sounds too exhaustive
Mariosavitch: we need a MAGA policy. Always winning. #1 in everything
madebyollin: "our L4 self driving vehicle powered by cutting edge exhaustive search"
Mariosavitch: since we fixed it.. can we lunar land
l1ght5p33d: how about "ideal search"
DeeboMC: @georgehotz can MuZero beat Bobby Flay?
l1ght5p33d: inputs ::: chemical affinity on toungue
Goooshlrific: exactly
phrixus_bro: nice
Waldoqq: LUL
Goooshlrific: WHAT
bobsmash: WutFace
DeeboMC: Lmao
jmv_chin: george is jammin out
bobsmash: hell yeaahh
727_tf: perfect
jmv_chin: LUL
leesingods: fire
Andremm2: lmao, was listening to lazy town this week
norlagg: LUL
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: @georgehotz rap on this beat or fake rapper
notoriousfats: no context, this is hysterical.
arakis_djall: Love this. Watching this all the way from Dubai over breakfast
bored_spagetti: just came here george quarantine is hitting you hard right ?
Kmerck313: Lol
l1ght5p33d: output: hamburger ice cream with cocaine
ViralVinnie4z: viralvinnie4z subscribed with Twitch Prime.
jmv_chin: ooo is that pheonix.js window manager tool or wut
DeeboMC: @l1ght5p33d 😂
ResonatorGames: Robbie Rotten actor died of cancer a couple years ago :(
rafablinder: De que se trata lo que estás leyendo?
2356drone: @rafablinder machine learning
l1ght5p33d: get it
techyimmigrant: Ooh a paper. Let's see the latex source.
Andremm2: Word
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: PogChamp
bored_spagetti: pepeD
theirishtripleking: ohh shit drop that beat Booooshhh
727_tf: oof
theirishtripleking: booooShh
Penguino138: So many raps to put on instrumentals
l1ttlemtman: yo
bored_spagetti: BARS!!
Kmerck313: Lol what the fuck
notoriousfats: what's going on
727_tf: @notoriousfats he's programming
badpartyhouse: yeyyy
badpartyhouse: yeeee
badpartyhouse: yeee
kuzan8: rap god
badpartyhouse: yea
notoriousfats: hahaha this is wonderful
techyimmigrant: A programmer trying to rap. Remain calm. It will end soon.
badpartyhouse: lets go
jezmezpez: OhMyDog
bored_spagetti: BARS!!
mashafique: bars PogChamp
borang: die twitch chat die
OW_RobotWizard: Popping off
badpartyhouse: yeeeee
Waldoqq: what is happenign
badpartyhouse: bum bum poww
qlutoo: 🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥
badpartyhouse: fireee
Penguino138: Tom Croose in the house
727_tf: pretty good
t0rment1337: god damn he got bars
Kmerck313: 🗑🗑🗑
superluminal86: george is an artist?
Krakatoa77: PogChamp
badpartyhouse: I support new career
bored_spagetti: NEATHERDALS TO JUNKIES SPIT THEM BARS OUT
jezmezpez: VoteYea
borang: cr00se
bobsmash: rap god
kaksoispistedeh: CurseLit
OW_RobotWizard: Fr tho thanks for getting me into development
bored_spagetti: lit
badpartyhouse: i will buy tickets to your concerts
vloood: based autist
bored_spagetti: faxx
OW_RobotWizard: Based
levorth: PogChamp
badpartyhouse: lets fund ComaAI with rap songs
birkett0011: Hes an Autist
leesingods: George did you see the UFO footage the gov released
Blatm: lol
notoriousfats: boom boom bap, boom boom bap
rafablinder: @2356drone do You understand that formula?
badpartyhouse: Lets buy open pilot with rap moneyyy
levorth: i can dance like micheal jackson
slurmdota2: its just 40
0xCheckM8: @georgehotz SupaHotFire
Mariosavitch: then play it backwards
Mrclutch963: What do you think about mr robot?
kaksoispistedeh: just build good vocal cloning EZ
DeeboMC: noah "40" shebib
rafablinder: entiendes el español?
2356drone: @rafablinder no lo entiendo wey no se nada de eso jaja soy un programador de backend
badpartyhouse: I will be the hype man
bored_spagetti: @mrclutch963 my favourite show ever what a character development
l1ght5p33d: you want a compressor
Musashhhi: watch logan paul vlogs, be a maverick
l1ght5p33d: muzero compressor
DeeboMC: i missed the rap. my stream dropped.. feelsbadman... thats my wheel house
2356drone: @rafablinder sí
DeeboMC: thats what the MC in my name is for
rafablinder: @2356drone hablas español?
Mariosavitch: why s[-1]? cant you just reverse the turn
Goooshlrific: on tic tac toe, a MTCS with a random playout should be good enough to be perfect. You should promote best practices and add unit tests!
vloood: lol dam writing unit tests for personal projects, couldn't be me
DeeboMC: logang
onlyonematt: @DeeboMC https://clips.twitch.tv/SpookyObservantShallotDoggo
DeeboMC: nice .. you the real mvp
rafablinder: @2356drone es tu lengua nativa?
l1ght5p33d: @Goooshlrific what best practices come to mind here
techyimmigrant: With TTT you just need a tree search. No need for ML algorithms. Meanwhile I spend my days messing with huge dataset generation for training DNNs.
2356drone: @rafablinder me puedo defender
2356drone: @rafablinder de donde eres wey?
rafablinder: Chile
badpartyhouse: We going to be here for a while if we do that
mangoxavier: Yes
rafablinder: Estudiaste progamación?
Mariosavitch: just pick random empty squares and see if you win
2356drone: @rafablinder soy de EEUU pero es de mexico mi novia
2356drone: @rafablinder si lo estudio
DeeboMC: hiding the horcruxes in starbuck's: top shelf shit
rafablinder: es necesario ser más inteligente de lo normal para entender esto?
Kmerck313: I used minimax algorithm to build a tic-tac-toe game
mangoxavier: Some good ass lines
vloodp: panter6Angry panter6Angry
doctorgenus: yeeiii boiiii
Mariosavitch: wont matter rofl
doctorgenus: does george like in a studio?
doctorgenus: is that his bed right there?
2356drone: @rafablinder ehh para entender machine learning quiza sí pero en general si lo quieras lo puedes aprender con el tiempo
DeeboMC: yea it would matter; strat changes
gigafact: did the chair change color?
ViralVinnie4z: must be a minimalist
doctorgenus: i think he got a new chair
mangoxavier: I think there’s a lamp or something.
DeeboMC: no but that pattern has the potential for maxtrixing effects
doctorgenus: maybe there was enough orders of the EON2's
doctorgenus: so he could afford the new chair
Goooshlrific: your ucb_score is wrong. Doesnt take into account player turn
mangoxavier: It’s a neural net chair
rafablinder: @2356drone me puedes dar un ejemplo concreto de lo que es machine learning?
mangoxavier: A 1
notoriousfats: rookie move
mangoxavier: Middle
Maccyhuge: hasMods
vloood: based chad, with a quarantine gf
doctorgenus: yeah i think he has a gf, but it sounds cooler say, i had this girl over
mangoxavier: This gets me pumped.
mediairfan: hi George how do you rate Chinese progressing in AI ...
DeeboMC: lol random girl wouldnt come back for her food
mangoxavier: I know women who would.
vloood: eating chinese food during corona, checkmate bigots
DeeboMC: bahaha
linux_____: @georgehotz what are your thoughts on nofap & does it really clear up brain fog?
mangoxavier: Maybe food was an excuse kna mean?
DeeboMC: touche
doctorgenus: or maybe the chinese food was really really good
mangoxavier: Probably.
DeeboMC: or the d
mangoxavier: Damn now I’m hungry
Goooshlrific: they're doing negamax where score on each node represents its score. That's why when they backpropogate they backpropagate with negative value. If you're doing it min max way, you have to just backprpogate value without negation (because the value itself will do that.
itsnahombereket: maybe she wanna come back and...finish it off he\ihihi
linux_____: where is ur favorite place to live?
doctorgenus: or maybe she's clingy and wants to see george again today
Penguino138: I was getting coffee what are you guys talking about girls for? haha
aloexai: George hii
aloexai: wassap George
aloexai: g'day George
happily0: @Penguino138 based chad streamer said he had girl overe
Penguino138: @happily0 who is based chad?
Goooshlrific: your node values switch from positive to negative right?
happily0: @Penguino138 george ofc
Goooshlrific: you say value *= -node.to_play
Goooshlrific: why negate that
Goooshlrific: just ignore the node to play
Penguino138: @happily0 nah george has alexxx
linux_____: JS > Py
EdwardApollo: Yoooooo
domenic367: thoughts on microdosinng lsd as a neutropic?
DeeboMC: george states "had girl over; leaves chinese food over; he informs her of such; she comes back to collect it" chat asks if he has a gf or if its a random girl; concludes he has gf but it sounds cooler to say "had a girl over".. to impy pimpingness... "chat deduces it must have been gf, not random girl, as only gf would come back for her food"... alternate theories then ensue. @Penguino138
l1ght5p33d: objectivley average and subjectively delicious
EdwardApollo: You inspired me to stream my self hapahazardly figure out how OP works, and figure out a location for a new feature
Penguino138: @DeeboMC Thanks for the detailed explanation haha
linux_____: I missed the girl..rate from 1 to 10 please
Goooshlrific: in negamax we never care about node to play
DeeboMC: lol no prob
DeeboMC: @linux_____ im not touching that
linux_____: understandable
itsnahombereket: NotLikeThis
Goooshlrific: except at terminal node
atlas193: How lone will it take to someone who doesn’t know programming to learn how to hack? I’m guessing a year or so.
atlas193: Long*
0xCheckM8: @atlas193 stop asking questions like that
EdwardApollo: code/hack bc you want to, don't worry about a timeline
atlas193: Uh is it prohibited in the stream?
l1ght5p33d: @linux_____ is your name like wheel of fortune or no
Goooshlrific: don't hack its illegal
EdwardApollo: lmao @Goooshlrific
prafaeltsantos: Good Morning(at least for me)! MVGame
Penguino138: @atlas193 They said stop asking questions like that because we like to stay on topic around here
DeeboMC: @linux_____ lmoa
legendarydarkstar: George i heard you already got the hack for ps5
legendarydarkstar: brother
DeeboMC: *elmo; tickle me elmo.. lmao
Penguino138: @legendarydarkstar we don't talk about sony or hacking
DeeboMC: that was supposed to be @l1ght5p33d
atlas193: Oh, I didn’t know what topic or context you were talking about, sorry.
legendarydarkstar: @Penguino138 but we lowkey have a cult built for that purpose
legendarydarkstar: and George here happens to be the leader
atlas193: So what do you talk about here?
Penguino138: @legendarydarkstar just stay on topic, people get banned for straying off and talking about unrelated things
Goooshlrific: is the model estimating reward for current or for first player?
legendarydarkstar: @Penguino138 yeah yeah i see the bottom of the chat
legendarydarkstar: i wish he was more lenant and takes jokes
l1ght5p33d: did anyone make muzero follower work
Penguino138: @Santiago_LHC Welcome, didn't see you made it to the stream till now!
DeeboMC: @legendarydarkstar either you're just talkin bs, ur deluded, or i missed the secret memo.. which of the 3?
atlas193: @edwardapollo Yeah I know, but I want to know how long will it take to learn what I’m about to learn.
t00big2fl4il: I was thinking about the last stream
Santiago_LHC: @Penguino138 Hey there
legendarydarkstar: @DeeboMC who you talking smack to?
atlas193: Out of curiosity.
t00big2fl4il: you were getting values that were looking wrong
legendarydarkstar: @DeeboMC Put some respek on my name
Penguino138: @atlas193 It depends on how dedicated you are, how fast you learn, and how fast you accumulate experience
theemadsnowcone: keeebroad
t00big2fl4il: I think it is all about the average isn't it large numbers
0xCheckM8: 1=x -1=o 0=empty, right?
DeeboMC: you dependngly upon the options above
theemadsnowcone: listen bois. im kinda drunk what is george up to today?
Goooshlrific: git push
DeeboMC: respek just ran out, sorry
0xCheckM8: git push so we can follow along here at home
mangoxavier: Git push git paid
Penguino138: yeah respek runs out when you argue with the people warning you to stay on topic :p
legendarydarkstar: @DeeboMC Say my name, get it right Whip it right, private flights Every night she keep it tight Choppas all at that red light H
DeeboMC: trash.. not the time tho
theemadsnowcone: @georgehotz what hoodie you wearin today
legendarydarkstar: @georgehotz
atlas193: @penguino138 Yeah I know that it differs from one individual to other, but is there an average time for new learners?
Goooshlrific: no don't add game ove!
t00big2fl4il: I could be wrong. but isn't it about the average. running the simulation millions of times and looking where it converges
atlas193: Nvm, it’s not that important.
Goooshlrific: itll ruin the ucb
legendarydarkstar: @Penguino138 Where I'm from, siga, it's respek, there's disrespek Then there's total disrespek and it's fuck everybody
DeeboMC: @atlas193 chill bro.. its a hard to quantify question anyway
Penguino138: @atlas193 thats like asking how long itll take you to become a professional athlete, it's highly depending on the work you put in!
l1ght5p33d: game over is some of the degenerate states?
gdawg7bb: So muZero is basically a state space model and a fancier ODE45 solver w/ a reward system?
legendarydarkstar: @Penguino138 Put some respek when you mention my name You talk about killers, but you ain't no killer Pull up on you, it's game time siga
Penguino138: @Santiago_LHC Keep an eye on legendarydarkstar
gdawg7bb: Or do I have that wrong
legendarydarkstar: no keep an eye on @Penguino138
gdawg7bb: It seems like a state space model in that it’s trying to linearize higher order differential systems
DeeboMC: anybody give af where dude is from? no. ok yeah thought so; just wanted to confirm we're all on the same page.
Goooshlrific: beautiful unit tests
Mariosavitch: that would be an integration test but ok
DeeboMC: @Santiago_LHC do it
t00big2fl4il: alloc how can't you know what alloc does? says the hacker friends
Goooshlrific: does the model correctly evaluate game over state?
t00big2fl4il: UUUNNIITTT test
atlas193: @penguino138 I see.
Mariosavitch: pytest
Penguino138: Whoever asked earlier, X and O moves are denoted by 1 and -1 not 0 and 1
t00big2fl4il: I hear you
mangoxavier: It should always start middle
mangoxavier: Always.
Penguino138: @0xCheckM8 you had asked, its -1 and 1
t00big2fl4il: UUUNNIITTT tests
Mariosavitch: integrationnnnnnn tests
Goooshlrific: does the model have UNIT TESTs on end states to verify correctness?
l1ght5p33d: underfit
l1ttlemtman: lol
ez_clappers_: @dejvid1998 hhkb
t00big2fl4il: don't get caught up on those outliers. If you run the simulation a large amount of times it will converge towards the true value. I think
Santiago_LHC: RPGGhosto
l1ght5p33d: 0 visit count what is this a net for infants
Mariosavitch: 0,3,1,2,5.. gg
opus_000: I'm a noob but I feel like there should be a better way
t00big2fl4il: isn't about training or learning
opus_000: can't you train a computer off optics?
t00big2fl4il: once you set it up and then you play it who ever goes first should win No?
tajpouria: Integrate that with react tic tak toe
Goooshlrific: can't you just use AI to debug it
icskarri: what' are your views on quantum computing
icskarri: @georgehotz
mangoxavier: Whoever goes first wins if they play middle. Or it will be draw. It’s stats.
Goooshlrific: uh well your model evaluates based on first player so you have to negate it as well which i think you do.
qazxswedcvfrtgbnhyujm: i think it's a problem that you're weighting everything equally when you divide by visit_count?
t00big2fl4il: don't worry about the minux
t00big2fl4il: minus
qazxswedcvfrtgbnhyujm: because a win that's found earlier in the search should be worth more
Goooshlrific: when you do select_child you want your worst child in negamax yeah
t00big2fl4il: doesn't it have to learn /reward itself for learning bad moves as well
Goooshlrific: so maybe you want smin= min([x[0] for x in out]) instead of smax = max([x[0] for x in out])
Goooshlrific: they doing max of negative
samuriia: Still not verified on instagram :(
Goooshlrific: which is min
info303: @qazxswedcvfrtgbnhyujm i think for that you would have to give negative reward on every extra turn
t00big2fl4il: the larger the tests the less frequent the bad nodes will become. it will have learned to avoid the bad moves at every step. remember in the Go challenge when the computer made a move midway through that no one understood
t00big2fl4il: and it turned out being the critical turning point in the match
mangoxavier: Should have started with Rock Paper Scissors.
l1ght5p33d: we want data structures
DeeboMC: is that a joke @mangoxavier ? thats not actually possible except with computer visoion or something
Goooshlrific: your values are correct, but your exploration and move choice is wrong
mangoxavier: That was a joke.
stephen422: !uptime
her3hero: any subs?
l1ght5p33d: add value to state struct
opus_000: could you use computer vision for tic tac toe?
Goooshlrific: flaky unit tests are the best. You just have to rerun them each one at a time until they all pass.
DeeboMC: ah i see.. but yeah even when you do build a rock paper robot like that, of course it can only -- effectively -- cheat anyway... except when you get into some weird pychology prediction modeling... super advanced ai for the least advanced game
gigafact: it's interesting how interested George is in this problem (MuZero)
t00big2fl4il: its going to get some wrong. it's learning NO?
DeeboMC: @opus_000 well i meant computer vision for anticipating sign before its fully made based off high speed anaylysis of hand movements; i dont know how itd be applicable to tic tac toe
opus_000: like if there computer saw the board determined use and just did it that way
mangoxavier: I mean u just assign a value to each hand pose. Nobody can actually see and react to the hand pose coming out irl
forkdb: Hello
l1ght5p33d: make asciii tic tac toe board
DeeboMC: oh ok; i thats what i was imagining the first time when i saw you had asked that, but i think that would be just adding an extra step (like for making a tic tac toe robot); however as far as ai would be concerned, its just an extra step: you'd only be using the vision as the means for collecting inputs that would go into the same kind of model he's building here.
DeeboMC: @opus_000
onu4r: georgeyboi hi
l1ght5p33d: mfw i don't know tic tac toe strategy
mangoxavier: Negative reward for each 2 in a row for opponent.
l1ght5p33d: you start in the center for sure right
Captain_Cavo: Lizard people control the world.... prove me wrong
DeeboMC: i actually dont.. i start in a corner if i start first
opus_000: the architect controls
her3hero: it doesn't want to play
mangoxavier: Throws up hands and is like “fuck it”
Goooshlrific: how about you never reward it. It's been a bad bot and doesn't deserve treats
sit_d: it's seen through the problem space - it'd shout wtf if you gave it a mouth
mangoxavier: Haha
Goooshlrific: you should write more sexy unit tests.
DeeboMC: then wouldnt it be bobby fisherin this bitch already?
mangoxavier: Bobby digital
DeeboMC: lol
fugebin: Kappa
mangoxavier: That’s p fucking smart tho
mangoxavier: Doesn’t mu0 not know the rules anyway
BrutalCSkAKAN: Test failing? Just comment it out
opus_000: computers need eyes
info303: assert(True)
DeeboMC: @opus_000 whats with you and copmputer vision lol
DeeboMC: i mean it has its applications but..
opus_000: I feel like this is antiquated almost
Goooshlrific: how about instead of backproping a value of 1, you backprob a value of like 100000. Then ucb score won't choose it again
l1ght5p33d: @opus_000 it is predicated
DeeboMC: and you think giving it eyes means its gonna have a brain?
info303: this is more cutting edge than computer vision I'd say
DeeboMC: biological anlagy notwithstanding
l1ght5p33d: @opus_000 95% sure full tree search is possible and is best just doing muzero things plus could train on non ideal play i gues
Goooshlrific: lol
Goooshlrific: a little hehe ex dee
Goooshlrific: this is why you should never write unit tests
opus_000: well yeah maybe.. set up a tic tac toe board, provide basic syntax principles and let it calculate the board
DeeboMC: @l1ght5p33d at that point we're talking about your ideas not his.
t00big2fl4il: the order matters for sure
Poselsky: Those tests look confusing.
mangoxavier: Ooh!
mangoxavier: Bong bong
t00big2fl4il: isn't it who goes first will always win
DeeboMC: @opus_000 that could be done all without vision
zetleri: illegal move from south
DeeboMC: you're taking vision and making leap from nowhere into logic
mangoxavier: SeriousSloth
DeeboMC: the ai has to come from somewhere. that somewher is agnostic of vision or not
jagger_rsw: Maybe you can simply allow for the model to choose between 1 and 9, and then do modulo (number of free slots) and use the chosen slot. No illegal moves :)
opus_000: idk the point is always to mimick biology first
balloonpopa: Is this the end Global Thermonuclear Warfare?
smurfd0: nice, congrats :)
mangoxavier: He’ll yeah!
mangoxavier: Middle
Binarylogin: 5
notoriousfats: 3
DeeboMC: we cant literally do that without ai systems in place. we cant build like nature does
zetleri: only winning move is not to play
t00big2fl4il: the middle square
mangoxavier: 5
rafaelbco: 5
zetleri: 7
Goooshlrific: your mcts creates child nodes for terminal states..
r3mote: r3mote subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 3 months! Good morning :)
mangoxavier: 3
t00big2fl4il: what was 5
Penguino138: @r3mote Welcome
t00big2fl4il: how is the grid numbered
mangoxavier: This is cool
notoriousfats: 0-8
FastCashCoding: is muzero not already playing?
mangoxavier: Diversity showing.
t00big2fl4il: so what was the key. that each player alternates? you hadn't built that in at first
DeeboMC: is there a ai tic toe site?
opus_000: will this be in GitHub?
Goooshlrific: wow 11
info303: i mean shouldn't it take forever since there are many more actions to run through if it doesn't know illegal moves
gigafact: https://github.com/geohot/ai-notebooks
Goooshlrific: oo 9
DeeboMC: does tic tac toe have ELO ratings, grand masters and strong tic tac toe engines to practice against?
Goooshlrific: no
Krakatoa77: tic tac toe is solved, optimal play always results in draw
DeeboMC: i was jk
PokerWeather: instead of penalizing ilegal moves wouldn't it be eat to tell it specifically what choices it has each turn?
t00big2fl4il: what is illegal. going where the other player has already played?
info303: ya
Goooshlrific: i mean connect 4 is also solved but has a rating system
Krakatoa77: lol
DeeboMC: the absurdity was funny to me
info303: connect4 is a cool one to train, but it takes forever
t00big2fl4il: can't you tell it that it can't do that
smurfd0: thats the definition of madness, doing the same thing expecting different outcome
info303: on a regular gaming pc that is
DeeboMC: but serious question: what about a tic tac toe site? couldnt what hes working on evolve to the engine behind such a site?
DeeboMC: because if one already exists, then i wonder what its using
chowzor: wouldn't tic tac toe learn pretty quick?
DeeboMC: you're watcing the same stream i am, buddy... seems like no
chowzor: I would imagine you could just hold the whole game tree in memory to test it, no?
DeeboMC: of course that depends on the algorithm
DeeboMC: ask george
chowzor: Well MuZero learns the rules,
mangoxavier: Try gungi next.
DeeboMC: ah i see
info303: u could just hardcode tic tac toe bot that would run super quick, but it wouldn't learn on it's own
DeeboMC: no hardcoding; i forgot
mangoxavier: This is amazing.
kkuette: Tic tac toe could be solve by ppo in matter of few episodes not the hardest game to learn
gary_burton: ...is it converging here...?
Blatm: What's muzero?
opus_000: will ai get to where it'll code things like this for itself ?..
DeeboMC: diffrent strokes for diffrent capitalists
sit_d: but it doesn't use past learning to learn new model :/
Krakatoa77: the point is to understand muzero and try it on simple problems to see if it works
Jehhred: Jesus, how many illegal moves does it want to make
kkuette: Fully observable envs are ez to solve :D
Siandemm: one game per second why its slow?
info303: the cool part of reinforcement learning is that it learns to develop better strategy by trial and error over many games
DeeboMC: so why not just test it against a hard code?
DeeboMC: until it starts stalemating
info303: u could, u could also train it against a hard coded bot
opus_000: idk .. a top down computation that beginnings from a visual determination of the game then assigns values and operations to calculate things
info303: but the latest model for chess developed in this way can now beat the best hardcoded chess bot 100% of the time
Krakatoa77: yeah but that won't work on harder stuff like Go because there isnt a hard-code for them, but muzero works on those problems too
chowzor: When I said quickly I mean less than a fewhours
Eclipshun: Hey George, have you heard about the startup Lex is working on?
DeeboMC: how can chess be hardcoded? im thinkining of hardcoding in the sense that it could be literally coded in logic gates
info303: chess has had bots forever
info303: like stockfish
bg7kd94: @info303 I dont think its 100% of the time for chess. But it is still by far the best program for chess
DeeboMC: you can build a circuit of it.... but those are ais essentially, no?
opus_000: senpai noticed me I'm honored lol
DeeboMC: ive got a book on beginnner circuitry where you can build a tic tac toe playing circit... thats what i meant by hardcoding
FastCashCoding: amazing...
mangoxavier: Go plus ultra
info303: oh, nvm, i used hardcoded incorrectly :)
DeeboMC: lol no np
info303: like explicitly written logic is what I meant in my case
DeeboMC: i see
info303: technically this bot should keep getting better and better the longer it runs
Krakatoa77: LUL
FastCashCoding: lets do it
zetleri: hell no
smurfd0: lets goo :)
Vjasal: how about regex
ViralVinnie4z: lol
bg7kd94: Doesn't that make sense that it shouldn't be good? It should take many cycles.
FastCashCoding: well beyond my skills
zetleri: as fun as rusty nail
luspr: @georgehotz Listened to your music while running yesterday. it was great. <3
chowzor: You're using what deeplearning framework?
mangoxavier: Yeah!
chowzor: PyTorch?
t00big2fl4il: implement it in Algol 60 please
info303: FORTRAN
amazon7737: !time
Waldoqq: COBOL MACHINE LEARNING PogChamp
t00big2fl4il: can I write a tic tac toe game that will be bundled in comma.ai?
Krakatoa77: So you are handling illegal moves by making them end the game and have huge negative reward?
DeeboMC: Still tho.. its mind boggling to imagine a chess engine being coded entirely in logic in the sense that you were using it. That’s really how stockfish was made?
opus_000: comma.bio
bruhsyfy: can you jail break my iPhone?
FastCashCoding: ban
opus_000: crispr me some new weed strains
bg7kd94: @DeeboMC yeah basically thats how stockfish was made
t00big2fl4il: it will be like the minesweeper of self driving cars. you can play at rest stops and gas stations, etc.....
DeeboMC: With nothing but if then statements?Wtf?! 🤯
huntboom: !uptime
shockWave2k11: Finally managed to catch you live
Krakatoa77: Afaik stockfish is somewhat like a minimax run using a heuristic value function, right?
info303: actually I have no idea how stockfish is made haha
bg7kd94: yeah thats what stockfish basically is
chowzor: @Krakatoa77 I think so
DeeboMC: @krakatoa77 now that makes sense
Krakatoa77: Like a hand-crafted value function
bg7kd94: stockfish is opensource I believe
chowzor: @Krakatoa77 They handcoded peice value and stuff
Krakatoa77: it's less AI-ish because you use human values on chess pieces and positions
Krakatoa77: @chowzor yeah
gigafact: I am blown away how people are willing to train Tesla AI for stop signs with autopilot enable stock so you have to push it every time to train it correctly...
djceci: just write an ai program that can program and ya got general ai eazy
mangoxavier: That’s chaos.
alexxxxxxxxxxxxxxx: Mister george have you ever taken an iq test? @georgehotz
t00big2fl4il: it wants to keep playing
DeeboMC: Coding a wining chess formula in if-then statements would be a code that’s literally miles long, I’d assume... can’t wait for an ai to code that
t00big2fl4il: last reward is negative
t00big2fl4il: have you told it what winning is?
huntboom: Interesting
DeeboMC: That’s a cool project idea for someone far more knowledgeable than myself
info303: hmm i think stockfish uses very different algorithms compared to this stuff
t00big2fl4il: weren't the earlier degenerate states absorbing states?
t00big2fl4il: absorbing states are states that it can't transition from?
DeeboMC: Yea I’m just talkin about doing something impractical for the shits n giggs.. like the guy who built a working cpu out of tinker toys and strings
djceci: if it programs in rust we will not understand the source anyway
opus_000: I want ai curated food recipes. maximum taste for my taste buds
lilou04: why chat so quiet
DeeboMC: @opus_000 , @l1ght5p33d already alluded to why that’s not happening anytime soon lol
Krakatoa77: @t00big2fl4il I think MuZero tackles the problem where you don't even know the rules, and that includes not knowing whether a side has won or not
opus_000: I'm just hungry
opus_000: future full of bioengineered foods seems great
DeeboMC: Haha understandable
DeeboMC: A la Star Trek replicator.. George was into that too if iirc
featuredloot: Is he done with COVID? What did his COVID research end on?
DeeboMC: Nvm, he was into the holodeck
l1ght5p33d: @opus_000 it would put drugs in the food
Klingenwetzer: PogChamp WE DID IT
Klingenwetzer: DAD
Klingenwetzer: 1 mil PogChamp
luspr: imagine there would be such a dashboard about cancer
Penguino138: @featuredloot long ago done yes
Eyachi: i mean the reason its so low is because we locked down it would be worse if we did nothing thats for sure
opus_000: 🤷🏽♂️
shockWave2k11: My Country is reopening next week PogChamp
njhypebeast: hello georgie i love you
DeeboMC: @eyachi you did it now lol
lilou04: india started producing a vaccine thats not even approved yet
DeeboMC: Ya dun goofed
Eyachi: oops. mb
sit_d: we should have a dashboard for all human killers
TheYoungBaboon: you havy any recommendations on ML courses or books? @georgehotz
DeeboMC: 😆
Penguino138: Straight wisdom from geo
t00big2fl4il: now they are saying a second wave
badpartyhouse: preach it
l1ght5p33d: why does anything happen every tho
webuser011: i think we need to stay home for the next 3 years
sit_d: it was another money grab
badpartyhouse: George Hotz 2024
badpartyhouse: lets get a vote in
badpartyhouse: who is down?
luspr: initially, the media narrative in February was that Corona panic is dumb, than it was "I want you to panic".
opus_000: i bet Trump's eyeing the debt to China as restitution
badpartyhouse: Facts
sophisticatedgaming291a11: completely agree
Penguino138: Wonder when the social norm will be no masks again
t00big2fl4il: one positive coming out of corona. I found twitch!
info303: on the bright side I welcome this new "work from home" culture! SeemsGood
birkett0011: I get to work from home tho
Sasukey7: target wont let me in without a mask
badpartyhouse: I never believed this bullshit from the beginning
lilou04: wait, is that a real policy?
JoneKone: Masks are a hotbeds for viruses.
luspr: In Germany I have to wear a mask grocery shopping and in public transportation by government mandate....
DeeboMC: I’m not sippin anyone’s kool-aid, George’s not excluded, too nihilistic to argue it tho; I just like to hear nuanced opinions either way
l1ght5p33d: I feel like we've been pretty adaptable
badpartyhouse: Yea
badpartyhouse: I got 4 sisters that are nurses, and they told me all about it
DeeboMC: Same but only 1 sister
badpartyhouse: they all have only about 4 patients out of 3 hospitals
badpartyhouse: This is in Seattle
webuser011: it is to see how far the y can control people
luspr: Now that people are all in panic they also cannot go back and say that the data is not as bad as they said.
t00big2fl4il: never let a good crisis go to waste
forkdb: Omg
badpartyhouse: 20 miles from the supposedly epicenter of Seattle
bg7kd94: Do people in general like to admit that they are wrong though?
b2kemann: people are sheeps, this is what it looks like on a big scale
DeeboMC: @bg7kd94 I don’t mind it if’s incontrovertible
JoneKone: Wait! What are we talking about?
badpartyhouse: Yeah but how do we change that with us keep doing our lifes?
l1ght5p33d: I've never worn a mask no one has said anything to me yet
badpartyhouse: some of us got businesses to run and don't have the time
Penguino138: @georgehotz when do you think the public will stop wearing masks, get back to normal etc?
GoldNux: Just got here, are we talking about the quarantine?
DeeboMC: Yea
TheYoungBaboon: you ever programmed on adderall i gotta know dad
Sasukey7: weren't u protesting
featuredloot: Voting bot?
b2kemann: i see the AI community i california is pushing hard for mask
lilou04: if they make masks mandatory in my country I'm walking outside with a balaclava
djceci: you cannot be sure with completely new virus what will be the outcome so that is why is the lockdown.
webuser011: newsom says he will keep CA shut longer because too many ppl on the beach
HopZe: i think it is fair letting people mind their own safety than enforcing upon them.
DeeboMC: People had the nerve to hassle you tho?
costcospizza: did bill gates wear a mask
ArosGeo: you're against having a lockdown? lol
limitless_64: I am a bot
badpartyhouse: How do we make the change when we got businesses to focus on? I just see the stupidity that happens but what are you going to do?
Krakatoa77: What's wrong with wearing masks?
HopZe: a lockdown cannot be permenant and there should be other solutions to this by now
ArosGeo: would that not make things worse, especially since cases haven't been going odwn?
HopZe: wearing a mask doesn't hurt anyone so I'm all for it
l1ght5p33d: actually there could be a really bad virus
ArosGeo: experts like fauci still seem to support the lockdown.
amanub: its exponential growth rate tho
l1ght5p33d: this one not so terrible
ArosGeo: yh but if you get it and give it to parents and such
itsxaos: if youre under 44 and dont smoke/arent morbidly obese
bg7kd94: cases have been going down
amanub: cause of the lockdown maybe?
HopZe: my mother has serious lungs issues so I cannot risk it geo
ArosGeo: part of why they arent going up in the worst case is because of the lockdown
Jeptah88: But this is with lockdown
amanub: dope bars
Penguino138: @georgehotz do you wear a mask at the store? Or just that one time you test drove ?
badpartyhouse: They are talking about putting patients under covid 19 even though they had other death symptoms
semihchelik: some young people may have an underlying condition that they might not know
lilou04: tomcr00se PogChamp
badpartyhouse: so that number is pumped up
l1ght5p33d: :: AIDS goes airborne :::
badpartyhouse: I think
Binarylogin: did you hear about the military wanting to use AI to track are panic buying among other things
Sasukey7: pretty sure corona struggles to spread outside
jagger_rsw: I can agree to some comments, but what do you mean by 'moving the goalposts'? It's not a discussion or a game with gov.
luspr: i feel like we go towards opening up though. All countries ale loosening restrictions. People will not accept them any longer.
ArosGeo: so that it stays flat...
semihchelik: they are scared of 2nd wave
bg7kd94: However the lockdown should end when we hit the peak right?
chunks____: it will stop being flat when you end the lockdown
JoneKone: @georgehotz Maybe you don't have a Grandma who could die for this, I mean I don't have a grandma anymore I do have my mom and her health is worth all the lockdown
JoneKone: You are talking bullshit
webuser011: so let your grma stay home
24786d: The hospitals are still inundated with sick
ArosGeo: they said they wanted lockdowns ASAP to flatten the curve. that doesn't mean they wanted to stop lockdown right after it flattens
ArosGeo: that's not moving the goal posts at all
Penguino138: @georgehotz do you wear a mask at the store? Or just that one time you test drove?
JdPaulBlart: hospitals are empty dude
badpartyhouse: they are not
ky0jinjaeger: I think it depends on your country's healthcare system, especially someone Euro countries that are overwhelmingly old
ArosGeo: no one said they wanted to flatten the curve and then remove the lcokdown straight after
badpartyhouse: I have my sisters tell me
luspr: @jonekone she should stay home. but you can go outsider
Jski101: 15 days to slow the spread, 30 days to slow the spread...
Forcepain123: There are only like 10% recovered in the US. Wait for more to be recovered then slowly open society more
smurfd0: https://covid19.healthdata.org/united-states-of-america
l1ght5p33d: hospitals are always smol inundated
webuser011: nyc isnt inundated either. they sent the hospital ships away and no one is using javitz
sit_d: google trend the term "flatten the curve"
luspr: in Germany, hospitals have less patients than usually.
t00big2fl4il: tomcr00se!
Penguino138: Should I not wear a mask then? There are a lot of old people at the store I go to
ArosGeo: what's the point of saying "covid isn't scarying if you're under 45", as if you can't get it and transmit it to older people/immunosupressed peopel
HopZe: do a google trends check
t00big2fl4il: when is Tomcr00se going to make a triumphant return?
mangoxavier: Hennessy insider
Jeptah88: But you can transmit it
costcospizza: they r doin an experiment to see how long people put up with it
badpartyhouse: yeah but 400,000 die from regular influenza
Jeptah88: Yes
r3mote: The curve is flattened just because we have a lockdown. If this is lifted too soon, the curve just goes up.
badpartyhouse: every year
luspr: I don't get why those statistics aren't all over the news. it's only scary anecdotes all the time
ArosGeo: don't you do stats? you understand your anecdote means nothing?
Jeptah88: That's anecdotal
JdPaulBlart: that graph is so manipulative
phottton: georgehotz So let's say we open up.. if we go exponential again we go lockdown or no?
newlastaccount: school
amanub: other people have different lifestyles
Penguino138: Are there any updates as to if it spreads by just heavier droplets?
alexxxxxxxxxxxxxxx: They are reporting every flu and obesity death as covid deaths, the lockdown surely has affected the regular flu transmission but the number of flu deaths surely isnt 0
Forcepain123: Because you are priviliged lol
Siandemm: Its deaths LUL
mangoxavier: The things I touch are under 45
HopZe: what about other people
badpartyhouse: the numbers just don't add up
Eolios: when they reopen I hope they follow strict procedure
ArosGeo: that's not flat lmao are you kidding yourself?
Forcepain123: A lot of people live with their grandparents / need to visit their grandparents
info303: i think the issue with this specific virus is that you can be asymptomatic for many days
phottton: georgehotz So let's say we open up.. if we go exponential again we go lockdown or no? <----
Siandemm: If you lose your leg you still not dead but you get it right
Eolios: I want to quit my job tho ebcause I work in the public but the benefits are too good
Sasukey7: looks pretty flat
smurfd0: we did in sweden have a if-you-can-stay-home thing...
webuser011: they should also be testing more now
itsxaos: they definetely have reacted though
Penguino138: @georgehotz I think the anxiety originally caused by the virus caused me more harm than anything. knowledge eliminates fear
badpartyhouse: Do you see the bullshit symptoms that the CDC listed?
Krakatoa77: But what about the hidden variable of testing rates?
mangoxavier: Antarctica killing this virus
djceci: the problem is that initially without any symptoms you can infect many other people!
alexxxxxxxxxxxxxxx: @georgehotz they are doing a self lockdown in sweden , but theres no law to enforce it
shockWave2k11: Not having an official lockdown doesn't mean that people didn't stay at home
Penguino138: @badpartyhouse yeah didn't the CDC say a dozen new symtoms that match with pretty much any cold?
badpartyhouse: Do you see the bullshit symptoms that the CDC listed????
phottton: alexxxxxxxxxxxxxxx we should do same
breadhamandegg: !uptime
b2kemann: their models for covid suck i realtime, and they expect ous to believe the climate change models....
costcospizza: ya it seems like a scam
vistamil: I may not have a grandma or any old ppl near me, but if I hang out with a friend that does, and I happen to be a carrier, he could pass it to his grandma. Sure, i dont see old people, at all, but other ppl i come in contact with probably do
Lourned: I live in NYC
amanub: 3Blue1Brown has some nice graphs boi check his video "simulating an epidemic"
Slybluedemon: don't Trump want to end it soon?
itsxaos: also consider that dieing isnt the only effect it can have
Penguino138: Can the MSM even turn back at this point? They've dug such a deep hole
Slybluedemon: doesn't*
itsxaos: its very possible there are long term health impacts from this
badpartyhouse: @Penguino138 yea its just ridiculous
ArosGeo: do you really think lockdowns do nothing? effective lockdowns absolutely work. you can look at simulations etc.
luspr: @georgehotz how do we prevent something like that in the future?
Eolios: a lot of misinformation constatnly spread
ArosGeo: there's a reason why it's being suggested, idk what you think the ulterior motive is
Penguino138: @ArosGeo he's not arguing for no lockdowns, he's saying it's been too long.
0xBADBADBAD: You do realize Sweden has one of the highest death rates in Europe?
Lourned: COVID Crisis aka Bailout 2020 Kappa
Jski101: Stopping the places helped
badpartyhouse: How do we change that?
phottton: I think we adopt Swedish method. All older people lockdown. All younger people go out. Also, don't fucking visit your grandparents
Jski101: planes* :S
DeeboMC: Sweden doesn’t have the same level of interconnectivity as the USA, just to be fair (in terms of nodal connection points/junctions)
alexxxxxxxxxxxxxxx: check Freeman Dysons view on climate change, he said the only reason he could speak about it was that he couldnt lose his job anymore
l1ght5p33d: catalytic converters are so good
JdPaulBlart: stuff is starting to open up again
badpartyhouse: if we don't have faith in the government
jagger_rsw: Isn't it best to assume that all politicians are saying whatever gets them to next term only? Still, our nations work somehow despite this.
rkxbz: of course, this planet is going to die soon
t00big2fl4il: don't let a good crisis go to waste
mangoxavier: If trump is re-elected climate change is fuckedforever check out chompsky on that
Trenz2: You know you
Krakatoa77: @georgehotz But what about the hidden variable of testing rates?
maxschneider96: The actual problem is that even the fast track designations by the FDA take too long atm. I hope in the future for urgent cases, drugs will be available for testing based on in-silico, ADME and toxicology modelling.
badpartyhouse: same
ArosGeo: @Penguino138 how is it too long though? they lockdown should continue until there isn't as risk of it growing again. no one said that hte lockdown should be ended once the curve is flattened
zetleri: @georgehotz Compare Sweden and Finland. The only diff between those is Finland had lockdown
Penguino138: @ArosGeo the lockdown is too long when they have to move the goalpost
Eolios: in california LA is the worse area think much less in other counties
masterfluox: Have you seen the ufo footages relased by pentagon? What do you think ? :O
peter35_: you a fan of moldbug?
ArosGeo: @Penguino138 which goalpost was moved? no one said the lockdown was just to flatten the curve. that was just part of it.
shockWave2k11: In Spain and Italy they sure were
phottton: Sweden isn't even ideal because they didn't protect their nursing homes. We should just dedicate more resources to test workers there and make sure they don't infect the elderly in the homes. Otherwise, we should just adopt what Sweden is doing
Penguino138: @ArosGeo The goal post to flatten the curve was moved
l1ght5p33d: 4 months of the world
mangoxavier: UFO vids were out last year.
luspr: it's also interesting that the only metric discussed is number of Corona cases. there are a lot of second order effects.
Eolios: Canada seems to be doing a fair job
DeeboMC: What about ufos?
costcospizza: they said an asteroid is flying by tomorrow
rkxbz: but are those deaths is caused by covid?
mich_mx98: @georgehotz Hello everybody! Is it worth a complete beginner in Java programming to read Horstman 1, 2 volume or better Shield complete guide 10th edition ???
badpartyhouse: I know you don't like Elon Musk
ArosGeo: moved to what? if you thought they were saying the lockdown was just to flatten the curve that's on you @Penguino138
DeeboMC: And freeman dyson is still alive?
badpartyhouse: What do you think of the new rocket
GoldNux: So what happend with the protein folding project?
alexxxxxxxxxxxxxxx: @DeeboMC he just died
itsxaos: what about long term health impacts? wouldnt it be worth it to prevent those?
mangoxavier: Pentagon declassified navy vids of ufo
phottton: georgehotz Mass General Hospital released their own simulator yesterday which informed MA governor extending lockdown here. You can play around with it here: https://analytics-tools.shinyapps.io/covid19simulator07/
hellostaliin: !time
Penguino138: @ArosGeo George just explained the whole concept of how they moved the goal posts
l1ght5p33d: guess illegal state
Krakatoa77: maybe increase mcts simulations?
vistamil: @mich_mx98 Just code. Choose a language and pick a project to work on
jagger_rsw: What do you think on the Iran's 'daily cases'? The smoothest curve I've seen :)
Binarylogin: I spend half the day watching that video b@geohotz
t00big2fl4il: just an idea. take Elizabeth Holme's edison machines and retool them to test for corona virus antibodies!
ArosGeo: @Penguino138 lol and im saying he's doing a terrible job. if you agree with him you should be able to explain the point too
Penguino138: @ArosGeo I respectfully disagree
maxschneider96: Due to the mutations there will need to be a new approach just like proposed by Baker Lab to make a universal vaccine based on strains on a patch.
smurfd0: you have the shortage of beds there
mich_mx98: @vistamil but as? if there is no base? aren't books needed? to become a really good programmer?
shockWave2k11: Can you link that model?
Goooshlrific: my former prof wrote a little preprint covid paper https://arxiv.org/abs/2003.07602
ArosGeo: why end the lockdown at the peak....the reason the peak wasn't higher was because of the lockdown
Penguino138: @ArosGeo We've passed the peak according to these models
Penguino138: 2 weeks ago
mangoxavier: Gonna wait for a few patches. Wait for world 2.1
jagger_rsw: Not sure what you mean by 'lockdown should end when the curve flattens'. those are correlated, no?
alexxxxxxxxxxxxxxx: @georgehotz Freeman Dyson who was the first to worked on computer models said most of them are flawed because if you do not have the perfect input date with just one parameter the output will come out totally wrong and we shouldn't really rely on them
t00big2fl4il: or take Elizabeth Holme's edison machines and retool them as ventilators. your thoughts?
24786d: The margin of error is large after a few weeks. I think the goal post was always meant to be moved after a few weeks.
alexxxxxxxxxxxxxxx: one of the first*
amanub: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gxAaO2rsdIs
ArosGeo: can we post links?
Penguino138: covid19.healthdata.org
mangoxavier: I’d not click them >.>
amanub: @ArosGeo no
ArosGeo: https://i.redd.it/iglg6dfue3v41.png they aren't predicting the past here, the projections were released before the actual dates.
t00big2fl4il: no you can't post links
l1ght5p33d: 1234
vistamil: @mich_mx98 Sure, but as you start coding you'll find yourself getting errors, you'll google and bit by bit you'll figure things out. If you wish to refine those skils, books/documentation/tutorials definitely help
Penguino138: 17 days so long ago man
ArosGeo: why would you expect lockdowns to stop at the peak? that doesnt make sense.
Goooshlrific: if you end lockdown models chsnge. they assune continuous lockdown
shockWave2k11: https://covid19.healthdata.org/portugal Lockdown here ending next week, the lockdown was effective as fuck
luspr: george, please, it's a moral imperative to stay home, huddle in a fetal position and watch panic news all the time
ArosGeo: no, i think the goalpost was never moved. people who think the lockdown was just to flatten the curve are mistaken.
Penguino138: ^
Penguino138: yeah its all about whether you're still in fear or have learned more about the virus
ArosGeo: the lockdown was expected to go on far beyond the peak and flattening of the curve
mangoxavier: Lmao goalpost moving. Is this a SEC game?
gullthar: Germany is fun. They state: 60% will contract it. Scares people to be good about health and then they are mad they did so well with it because, observer bias.
semihchelik: fuck corona lets get back to tic tac
ArosGeo: you're probably thinking of models that showed the worse case stuff
ArosGeo: idk maybe because you only read headlines lol
webuser011: Johns Hopkins maybr
jagger_rsw: Again, might agree with some comments, but since lockdown and cases affect each other, why say 'stop lockdown if the curve flattens'
amanub: @ArosGeo maybe
badpartyhouse: Trump was right to re open the economy
JdPaulBlart: bill gates wants lockdown until this time next year
AndrewPine: Imperial College models maybe?
DeeboMC: @jagger_rsw this ☝🏽
someguy202020: remove lockdown, if cases and deaths go up, go back to lockdown
costcospizza: thats life buddy
Lourned: Trump is the president, that should tell you something about government in the US, he is a businessman btw Kappa
mangoxavier: Ants are constantly warring ...
Penguino138: People also need to realise every place is different, like NY might require a longer lockdown, but doesn't mean anywhere else has to adhere to that
Bombapil0t: I'm proud to be an ant
l1ght5p33d: The problem is public perception of numerical facts
mangoxavier: Ants never stop killing other colonies. They are the worst analogy for an anti-gov stance lol
luspr: they corrected this number downwards
Penguino138: First Model: 2 million deaths Second Model: 100k-240K Third Model: 64K Fourth Model: Who cares
lilou04: what countries didnt had a lockdown beside sweden?
DeeboMC: fuck the rona
sit_d: where's the model that says inject disinfectants?
Krakatoa77: Didn't the models assume complete lockdown though
maxschneider96: https://www.ipd.uw.edu/2020/02/rosettas-role-in-fighting-coronavirus/
jagger_rsw: It seems you finally agree with Musk on this :) - https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1255380013488189440
Phibz1: what is transmision rate factor R in US?
Lourned: LUL
lilou04: LUL
KSDiamaiD: @lilou04 in BW in germany there never was a lockdown
QED__: LUL
Penguino138: Elon been trolling since the beginning of the pandemic :p
techied: top kek
luspr: remember when masks where stupid and now they are mandatory?
badpartyhouse: I think you got balls
Klingenwetzer: forsenKek
GS540: read the replies LUL
Klingenwetzer: it never was
Bowlgirlblergh: breaking news: tesla stock plummeting
lilou04: @KSDiamaiD yeah but countries not certain regions
Bowlgirlblergh: atpRtsd
l1ght5p33d: actually the reporting of figures is probably actually technically wrong a good amount of times
semihchelik: hahs
birkett0011: LUL
Lourned: Corona on the Mars confirmed
Beraton: elon for president
Penguino138: Everyone has their corona panic moment, it's about educating yourself and getting past it
kayoeyumisaolegais: !uptime
hovax99: The amount of tests done is most likely very different in different countries, very hard to compare countries using this number... Only numbers in Sweden that is almost correct, is the number of people in hospital and the number of dead.
luspr: @ksdiamaid sure there is a lockdown in Germany. you cannot have guests in your home or go to a restaurant.
mangoxavier: TheIlluminati
peter35_: make snowcrash real
RealOden: corona sent to space with elons car FeelsBadMan
vistamil: He's going to be trending by the time ppl wake up.. lol
KSDiamaiD: @luspr thats not what a lockdown is....
semihchelik: take out flamethrowers
alexxxxxxxxxxxxxxx: theres a lockdown in every country except north korea, in some though it's a self lockdown and theres no law to enforce it
Lourned: all computer people complaining about lockdown while living pretty much in lockdown their entire life Kappa
techied: nk doesn't need lockdown cause if you cough you'll get shot and thrown in a river
mikey9988: atpRtsd
Bombapil0t: +1 @Lourned
jagger_rsw: Make some arrangements for the future then if this all crosses your pain threshold. If something like this appears ever again, move to Sweden for a couple of months.
l1ght5p33d: I do what I want, how I want, where I want, when I want
webuser011: in nk if you need to cough you just jump in the river
RealOden: sweden borders KEKW
smurfd0: jup we dont let people in
GoldNux: We want you here.
t00big2fl4il: ventilator.ai big contract from the government!
Forcepain123: I am in Germany and we have to wear masks now, we have like 1000 cases per day... declining heavily. I feel like we do way too much
Lourned: Volvo is a good car
Bombapil0t: you are in the cloud Hotz
b2kemann: volvo is no longer i sweden
decap__: stores
Forcepain123: public transport, stores
Penguino138: In stores is more dependent right?
TyButNowYouDie: stores and bus/train
DeeboMC: Pull up with a case of Corona, they’ll welcome you.
RealOden: Sweden doesn't even have quarantine, people just live their lives and told to stay at home if they feel sick LUL
DeeboMC: A case of corona beer
shockWave2k11: Elon Woke
techied: RealTalk
Bowlgirlblergh: what is so bad about staying at home though
peter35_: based
Binarylogin: #truth
semihchelik: facts
info303: lol i mean that's been the story for decades :D
Sasukey7: fucks the economy
decap__: what freedoms we talking about?
costcospizza: did elon join the Q
DeeboMC: Says the South African national
jagger_rsw: despite your 2nd amendment, it didn't prevent the 'tyranny of gov', if you see it as such :)
Penguino138: the only thing thats gonna change when everything opens is we can go out and get food and bring it home to program
l1ght5p33d: i can kill you with my cell phone
Bowlgirlblergh: are police stopping people from being outside though?
bob_4202: i can't run c++ file in sublime :((
J3rwin: O.o
gullthar: fuckin'2d!!
siolentnight: you cant run c++ file period @bob_4202
shockWave2k11: Joey Saladas is fucking idiot
Super_car_car: joey salads LUL
Lourned: hey corporations got trillions bailout moneys, winning! Kappa
bob_4202: @siolentnight oh i see
Forcepain123: LUL
knysh: LUL
ArosGeo: that guy has literally drank his own piss on video
Bombapil0t: That's no longer your right. You are playing with the health of the general public and thus become a potential threat. Keepo
decap__: right wing maniacs l;ol
itsxaos: people need to stop lying
FUSiONPlays: agree
DeeboMC: “Smartest man in the world” 😑
info303: the truth is out there.. *x-files theme song*
b2kemann: people like crisis, because then they can go out and play heros
FUSiONPlays: i don't like how lying about these things to achieve some sort of political highground is acceptable
xendorize: People don’t want to watch the truth if it’s moderate
gullthar: aw shiiit
dingletoast: Huh. First thing I see when I arrive is a covidiot
d14rgt: pffff Joey Salds LMAO
Penguino138: Watch the intro to "Alex Jones vs Bill Gates Part 2"
techied: georgehotz dunno if you've already said, opinion on proximity tracing?
waynzcore: would it be better to say "please noble americans stay home!?"
mangoxavier: Some places doing fines for leaving. That’s bad.
RealOden: What happens if you go outside in US?
Penguino138: You get fresh air @RealOden
RealOden: Holy shit making it sound like you get shot on sight
vloood: lol who's lying, ifr is still ~1% pretty much, with r0 ~3
bojosos: The protest worked?
lanop24: I agree with what you saying, however people don't listen even when you ask them nicely.
Sasukey7: u get so distracted
Klingenwetzer: so is the earth flat or not? forsenThink
bolleys: Hey pap
DeeboMC: Final thoughts: Rather have a case of modelo than a case of corona ✍🏽™️©️®️
gullthar: imGlitch
b2kemann: @Klingenwetzer it's flat for you
xendorize: @lanop24 I agree, I can try to stay aaay
vloood: yes it does
data__love: That's only NYC and the sampling was grocery shopping, not random.
luspr: George, ever considered doing a podcast?
gullthar: it's arcgis?
Klingenwetzer: Only on my screen forsenThink
mangoxavier: More likely to get hit by commaai car than get corona.
xendorize: 6 feet away from people and wear a mask, but I can’t control what others do
justMemo: can you please send a link for the map georgehotz
markydothh: Merica! Freedom!
Klingenwetzer: since I got no curved monitor
vloood: you have to look at fatalaty numbers from when that study came out, but it was around 1%
Penguino138: Use NY State not City
vloood: lmao
Krakatoa77: 10e6 is 10 million
Eolios: for states and counties with low cases or none should be able to open
Bombapil0t: no commaai talk NotLikeThis @mangoxavier
markydothh: So George supports States opening up?
Eolios: like Nebraska has low cases
b2kemann: QUICK MATHS
mangoxavier: BlessRNG
vloood: it's nyc not state
gullthar: so... slow burn?
Penguino138: 8.99 million was the city population
vloood: 21 was city
Krakatoa77: @georgehotz 10e is 10 million not 1 million
markydothh: THis is why the US is so fked
DeeboMC: Rather talk about that then this bullshit
Forcepain123: @vloood shouldn they assume that there are a lot of untested people?
markydothh: Smart guys advocating opening up when it means covid spreading
Forcepain123: @vloood who already have had it without symptoms
data__love: Test was NYS but the NYC figure were very different
luspr: i think state was like 16 %
Krakatoa77: 10e6 is million
Krakatoa77: 10 million*
l1ght5p33d: we want protiien printing
Lourned: wait what 19 million in New York State? California has way more people wtf
Penguino138: Yeah but NY is much desner
l1ght5p33d: we want virus manufacturing
Penguino138: *denser
vloood: wait ur doing the math wrong here, lemme pull it up
gullthar: it was HOUSE MD
Lourned: @georgehotz you probably didnt count illegal immigrants
Krakatoa77: @georgehotz 8.3 * 10e6 is 80 mill not 8 mill
data__love: You're off by a zero
data__love: 10e6
Lourned: LUL
Sasukey7: lmao
t00big2fl4il: the only swines are the politicians
bojosos: Not all sick people have died yet
Eolios: how is the rest of the new york doing
Bombapil0t: :D
l1ght5p33d: for self immune based cures
Penguino138: @georgehotz Do you think we're any more prepared for a pandemic?
Jehhred: Don't you have work tomorrow george?
Choruptian: hi, how's muzero treating you
Eolios: https://covidtracking.com/data
t00big2fl4il: Yo. what did you think of Nancy Pelosi's sick ice-cream stash?
l1ght5p33d: @Jehhred geohot is actually mark zuckerburg in the daytime
Penguino138: Yesterday it was 3x flu, now 2x. #Science
janpoonthong: what are you making?
techied: l1ght5p33d how dare you compare geo to that piece of shit
itsxaos: are you worried at all about long-term health impacts
bojosos: How are people using rats to test vaccines? Do ratwbeven get covid
t00big2fl4il: search it
luspr: imagine if all the capital allocated to Corona would go towards cancer or Alzheimer's. how many lives we could save.
Bombapil0t: @l1ght5p33d never ever do that comparison again
t00big2fl4il: politicians out of touch with the everyday person
b2kemann: looked at wolframs new theory of physics?
b2kemann: pretty neat
forkdb: Yaloo
gullthar: it was the watership
krispeer: @luspr imagine how many lives would be lost
Forcepain123: Forcepain123 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
Penguino138: @b2kemann He needs to get it peer reviewed
DeeboMC: What does George think of zuck in terms of skills anyway?
b2kemann: fuck peer review
lilou04: Based Elon
Penguino138: Elon staying up late going hard af
badpartyhouse: What do you think about th erocket
techied: wow
smurfd0: savage
badpartyhouse: rocket?
mangoxavier: Squid1 EarthDay Squid2 TheIlluminati Squid4 🏡
l1ght5p33d: usa is the moral elite
techied: he finally saying what you been saying lol
bojosos: Are you going to Mars with all the twitch money?
forkdb: What do you feel... when Elon buys comma for couple of billions?
luspr: Elon said in March that the Coronavirus panic was dumb
l1ght5p33d: trump gave away so much wellfare it's become a moderate paradise here
bojosos: you did
vloood: yes you did it wrong, i'm trying to work it out, nyc is 1% ifr
gullthar: do it for kimbal
b2kemann: https://writings.stephenwolfram.com/2020/04/finally-we-may-have-a-path-to-the-fundamental-theory-of-physics-and-its-beautiful/?source=frontpage-latest-news
Penguino138: Don't forget NY State not city
Rudolfkeil: NY State, not City
vloood: told ya
Penguino138: ah ok
vloood: with r0 =3, require 65% for herd immunity
Penguino138: But probably only 5x in dense regions
markydothh: Why did he take 0.2 of nyc pop?
luspr: In Germany, ifr was estimated to be 0.4%
zthreee: It was in Santa Clara County, not NY
Bombapil0t: now its about 5x flu ? #science
badpartyhouse: respect
zetleri: Its hard to read comments on elons tweet :D
smurfd0: also take in concideration that most data ofthe flu is from the whole last year, corona has not been here half a year yet
markydothh: He saying 20% of total population has contracted Covid?
DeeboMC: I want @georgehotz ‘s personal insight into how weird the zuckbot actually is.. thinking he may avoid it because Instagram career suicide
zthreee: https://www.medrxiv.org/content/10.1101/2020.04.14.20062463v1 The problem with this study is, that it is very wrong in terms of mathematical models. The age median was 34 for example and they didnt mention it.
vloood: yeah that's only a problem in santa clara
vloood: where positive rate is low
vloood: in new york, anitbody test will be more accurate
24786d: If this the same study I read about, they sampled people at grocery stores.
presidentkanyewest2024: hi
alexxxxxxxxxxxxxxx: The only reason i believe the lockdown is good is because it will have a huge effect on other human transmitted diseases like influenza
jagger_rsw: Tell me ze end game
vloood: yeah that's fine, that's a policy question, but i don't think it's crazy to say 1 mil + ppl could die from this
DeeboMC: “Begin privacy enhanced message”
t00big2fl4il: back in the rabbit hole! you have to go into the rabbit hole willingly without any guarantee of return! that is where the true learning occurs!!!! tomCr00se must return
Klingenwetzer: the whole herd immunity thing ResidentSleeper
adamiscool8: adamiscool8 subscribed at Tier 1.
luspr: ifr = 0.37 % https://www.land.nrw/sites/default/files/asset/document/zwischenergebnis_covid19_case_study_gangelt_en.pdf
lilou04: didnt they wanted corona tracking system on every phone?
badpartyhouse: yea
DisHonoredNoble: 39k
adamiscool8: extra 20%
presidentkanyewest2024: its true because they get more money then
badpartyhouse: more vunding
vloood: if anything corona is undercounted
DeeboMC: Probably
GoldNux: please grow a beard and go full Eddie Bravo
vloood: because of deaths at home
vloood: i woudl say 1% is lower bound
vloood: excess deaths statistics most valualble
vloood: you can't fake that
Klingenwetzer: there is always an uncertanty when humans are involved
vloood: they lag too much
vloood: hard to use them
eksdee_1_2_3: i thought it would be at like 100 million infected by now....
Klingenwetzer: xD
DeeboMC: I know ideas > events > people but can we stop this boring shit and talk about Zuckbot and grilled meats, etc
Klingenwetzer: ppl are scared
badpartyhouse: people are pussies
Bombapil0t: either they don't know the truth or they're keeping it from public.
Binarylogin: they just want to control the food supply where is my Trump meat at
vloood: it's basically less lethal but more contagious than spanish flu, averages about the same potential impact
badpartyhouse: true cause people live over leveraged
Penguino138: People are scared because they're not educated on the subject
mashafique: Communication in 2020 LUL
badpartyhouse: they are scared of the dept that they have
ahmetomerv: Stopped looking at models except victoria secrets ones
b2kemann: all is gonna change once biden is the president <3
Klingenwetzer: call it precision loss LUL
fizziblytwitching: George, you're assuming a level playing field
shrewduser: reminds me of BP after the oil spill
mashafique: That's the problem. People don't like to admit their mistakes.
fizziblytwitching: You assume that everybody reasons about these tings
alexxxxxxxxxxxxxxx: @b2kemann stop trolling
semihchelik: Trump would be the last person to do that
info303: i think you overestimate average intelligence of citizens
socialnotsocial: Have you read Nassim Taleb? What do you think?
peter35_: we're deeeply sorry
Santiago_LHC: Boeing CEO should go: "Is the plane perfect? No, but it's cheap and you have better odds than with coronavirus"
TheRealMast3r: I'm just following Nassim Taleb on Twitter, he has a strong anti BS filter and is good at stats
techied: its like the South Park BP parody
GoldNux: At the beginning of the 21st century, the Apple Corporation had become the largest commercial entity in the United States. Nine out of every ten homes contain its products. Its political and financial influence is felt everywhere. In public, it is the world's leading supplier of computer technology, medical products, and healthcare. Unknown, even to its own employees, its massive profits are generated by military technology, genetic experimentation and viral weaponry.
shockWave2k11: The bi party political system is a joke
shrewduser: USA can't seem to get a break and have a good president for a change
t00big2fl4il: wow long message
Klingenwetzer: LUL not false
jagger_rsw: unless you're D.Knuth
DeeboMC: Ideas > events > people > COVID-19
mashafique: It's 5Head time bois
shockWave2k11: Down another rabit hole we go
l1ght5p33d: no way commander in chief with private cia army
lanop24: people are scared of admiting when they are wrong, beats me why
t00big2fl4il: lets go tomcr00se! lets go!!!!!
shrewduser: the western world is going through the opposite of the enlightenment atm
peter35_: presidents are distractions
Klingenwetzer: I mean this whole president debate only comes up because of all of the scandals revolving around trump
l1ght5p33d: us has been fucking around since day 1
t00big2fl4il: tomcr00se that's some funny sh&#! bring 'em back please?
Klingenwetzer: lmfao
shrewduser: sure but he's kind of a symptom of a bigger problem
Klingenwetzer: KKona HELL YEAH
costcospizza: thats the business
l1ght5p33d: executive orders and cia private army
gigafact: It's always upsetting when someone you care about dies so I understand why people panic...
sircrocodile163: ..and then you die in millions LULW
b2kemann: the president symbolizes who is currently leading the culture war
DeeboMC: @jagger_rsw what was the Knuth reference about? I missed that
kernelimage: Yep!
Klingenwetzer: LUL
Klingenwetzer: forsenHead
lilou04: too soon
GoldNux: pools closed
djceci: just dont forget to drink your favourite bleaching agent and ya must be safe
Krakatoa77: LUL
b2kemann: yes it's stupid
presidentkanyewest2024: trump cloesed borders early and they called him racist, now the same people are saying he didn't close them early enough
Klingenwetzer: "Pools"
Sycto: how many kids skating did it take to make this happen
jagger_rsw: @DeeboMC that programmers make mistakes (exc. D.Knuth)
payrate: @georgehotz can I just first say I stumbled upon your stream on YT, you were doing some hi-tech programming, it was great! Anyway, I just want to comment on that Boeing thing you said, I agree with you and to back your argument up even more: people today want the truth more than ever couse we are sick of the lies. Almost everything we see today in movies and TV, online are all about showing "How it's made"
t00big2fl4il: tom. just some quick hacking CTF advice. por favor
shrewduser: you're above it all until you aren't
DeeboMC: Lol oh i see @jagger_rsw
stephen422: george you not sleepin
luspr: Can't we just build the future instead of having a culture war?
mashafique: People just want something to be outraged at times LUL
Klingenwetzer: I mean all countries in the EU closed borders
kernelimage: Lol I saw this
Santiago_LHC: How many seconds away are we from going deep on Kim Jong Un speculation
MllCZ: we need a gamer as the next president
presidentkanyewest2024: hes dead
sircrocodile163: but there is no future for NA LUL
info303: omg best idea! livestreaming everything the president is doing
DeeboMC: @santiago_lhc hopefully not too long
qlutoo: Can I be your VP
adorablejaay: nathanGodstiny Gamergate destroyed nathanGodstiny
TheRealMast3r: Why do you put the troll in the center with your hands @georgehotz Kappa
itsxaos: if you become president youll be assassinated before you can cash your twitch subscriber check
Shleeable: the dude who runs the Australian CIA publicly accused China of making it in a lab... Lying wins votes
xendorize: Three groups, names four
alexxxxxxxxxxxxxxx: I think the presidents main role is to be a crises manager and unite people, trump is very bad at that, the second most important is to be a good policymaker which trump i think is somewhat good at.
Klingenwetzer: the trolls :tf:
alexxxxxxxxxxxxxxx: crisis*
t00big2fl4il: hacking! they can't ruin hacking. spoken by tomcr00se sage advice
luspr: So the trolls are winning?
Klingenwetzer: forsenK Trolls are the ppl that keep things interesting
l1ght5p33d: VIM > EMACS
gullthar: bulldozers are winning
payrate: What is "the culture war" we are referring to here? I am an uneducated scum
lilou04: how?
semihchelik: no trolls no problem
gigafact: what is Elon saying?
kernelimage: LOL
techied: nano > vim
fizziblytwitching: Except no one wins
Klingenwetzer: KKona FREEDOM
t00big2fl4il: hacking!
b2kemann: trolls are atleast smart enough to not take it serious
fizziblytwitching: It's a big games of fuck ourselves
shrewduser: you know what's crazy, in the bay area, you're in the richest part of the richest country yet you have the shittiest third world infrastructure. where does all the money go?
DeeboMC: @b2kemann this ☝🏽
okeeeeeee: you are a troll too, dont deny it @georgehotz
eksdee_1_2_3: sanctmonious is a big brain word
gullthar: it's at recognition tho
Klingenwetzer: george is one handsome boi :3
Jehhred: @eksdee_1_2_3 Because alliteration
presidentkanyewest2024: cant why for kanye as president
jagger_rsw: @payrate I think he talked about gamergate (wikipedia it)?
fizziblytwitching: @georgehotz did you watch AlphaGo?
l1ght5p33d: always wanted more action
eksdee_1_2_3: alliteration is a big brain word
Klingenwetzer: nymnREE
DeeboMC: Phew.... glad that’s over
gullthar: so . . . sort of?
payrate: Thank you sir @jagger_rsw I did, I am educated now.
Santiago_LHC: @eksdee_1_2_3 read a book
t00big2fl4il: hacking will always win!
eksdee_1_2_3: N OMEGALUL
Klingenwetzer: nymnCV 👉 📈
jagger_rsw: @payrate this article is like 5 min long, too early, too early :)
DeeboMC: U a battle rap fan? @georgehotz ... noice
payrate: @jagger_rsw aha! Another European, I see! PogChamp
jagger_rsw: @payrate si
payrate: @jagger_rsw Vamos a la playa, salut from Sweden, hejhej!
eksdee_1_2_3: is he using vim
Klingenwetzer: I've been awake since 6pm CEST ResidentSleeper
jagger_rsw: Vamos a mi casa, por la ultima
payrate: @jagger_rsw Gracias Muchacha! I am coming right away!
maxschneider96: Coronavirus is just the beginning btw, u´ ll need to come up with better strategies in the future. There´ s also many pathogens in permafrost including the spanish flu that could have a comeback
Klingenwetzer: EL NO SABE forsenKek
l1ght5p33d: sagemaker smash
Klingenwetzer: forsenS
socialnotsocial: Have you read Nassim Taleb? What do you think?
b2kemann: death is just a transformation
Bootstraps: did we resolve the issue?
presidentkanyewest2024: can't wait for the Corona 2 release
StopitDonk: can i have your BCH if your on deaths door?
sircrocodile163: I will twit at you what moron you were LUL
Klingenwetzer: nymnTF
Jehhred: No one: Government & Media: <Insert Fear Mongering Here>
semihchelik: one less ant
Klingenwetzer: nymnS
Santiago_LHC: "Engineered pandemic"
lanop24: Been through one war in my life time already
info303: superintelligent ai is at 5% lol
presidentkanyewest2024: nanotechnology accident monkaS
payrate: @georgehotz you should go on Joe Rogan podcast, I'd imagine you make a really interesting convo!
Bootstraps: LUL
StopitDonk: DO IT!!
sircrocodile163: DO IT
presidentkanyewest2024: LUL
Binarylogin: do it!!!
l1ght5p33d: wikipedia is all that is good and holy
StopitDonk: ' edited by george hots.'
sircrocodile163: JUST FOR 10MIN
Klingenwetzer: what if we all would drink bleach? Then there would be no wars and no corona virus that could spread PogChamp
jagger_rsw: I think we need to create another state, or at least a church, with our own rules re pandemics. The church of st. george's twitch channel. I think it gives some tax benefits also
Incurs0: LUL
Santiago_LHC: "Bat eating = 25%"
maxschneider96: @Klingenwetzer hahaha
bojosos: Engineered pandemic has higher probability so coronavirus is human made
gigafact: George look at this https://twitter.com/fredhassen/status/1255262850290978819 impressive
osuiw: so george, you've been exercising lately?
payrate: @jagger_rsw I honestly believe for the world to become "2nd lvl" it needs a common enemy. Humans are still in the cradle, like it or not, but we are still stupid no matter how smart we think we are.
Bootstraps: how did they do that
l1ght5p33d: Just wait till the day they release a feature that breaks
mathematician9: good morning from Greece
bigie: Good morning
socialnotsocial: Have you read Nassim Taleb? What do you think?
jagger_rsw: George, create a church, I can be a high priest, you can be pope
bojosos: US de
payrate: Aliens doesn't need to be the "common enemy" Sir @georgehotz
info303: NOO, then they will unglug the simulation...
info303: unplug*
presidentkanyewest2024: restart your computer 4Head
bigie: george have you seen stephen wolfram's physics model ?
l1ght5p33d: add gpus
lilou04: lets raid area51
luspr: I think you need a positive vision of the future, not a common enemy.
t00big2fl4il: qira! that sh1t!
Klingenwetzer: maybe 100% concentrated acid would be more efficent for removing wars and corona at once?
presidentkanyewest2024: pretty sure hillary clinton is an alien
bojosos: more compute
jagger_rsw: get FW of an alien spacecraft, qira it, win
maxschneider96: @Klingenwetzer if there was such a thing lol
StopitDonk: i still think this was our christmas present from mr. Kim
payrate: @luspr hit me with a positive vision of the future, I am so far away from imagining one...
b2kemann: @bigi i one up this +1
covidneunzehn: trololololololol
l1ght5p33d: not bad
t00big2fl4il: heck yes.
Bootstraps: george how many days do you work from home?
DeeboMC: Wolfram = the big brain man’s big brain
Krakatoa77: @georgehotz Can you explain how the dynamics network (g) learns?
b2kemann: wolfram is on another level
Jehhred: Now put it in a GUI and let us beat the model
Klingenwetzer: well we the lockdown in germany got lifted for the most part FeelsGoodMan
Binarylogin: #learn wolfman next project
b2kemann: that would be an awesome stream project
freshsoclean: y arent u using lingo
b2kemann: computational research
gullthar: keep searchin' ya'll sayanora
covidneunzehn: please start to hack gov's all over the world to bring up and spread the truth
andrey18106: How many years you are involved in programming?
b2kemann: read the chat geo!
t00big2fl4il: qira tha monte carlo! TOOOOOMMMMcr000000000ssssseeee! Let's go!
payrate: @covidneunzehn isn't that why Wikileaks founder is in jail?
Dino_hun: Hey, what's up! Lovin the stream ;)
Klingenwetzer: it just works 4Head
b2kemann: https://writings.stephenwolfram.com/2020/04/finally-we-may-have-a-path-to-the-fundamental-theory-of-physics-and-its-beautiful/?source=frontpage-latest-news look here
DeeboMC: @georgehotz doing some wolfram shit
Klingenwetzer: good ol' trial and error
jordangleanuk: this is common sense
DeeboMC: wolfram vs langan's ctmu?
Klingenwetzer: DansGame
yogi_1010: WutFace
Androzzo: pee?
StopitDonk: pee pee time
covidneunzehn: Kreygasm
Androzzo: ahaahahahha
Klingenwetzer: lmfao degen @covidneunzehn
covidneunzehn: didnt wash hands
Androzzo: lol
Klingenwetzer: DansGame DIDNT WASH
StopitDonk: didnt wash hands
Klingenwetzer: forsenWhat forsenWhat forsenWhat
Dino_hun: wash hands
xbullll: Hello George
Androzzo: dont need to wash
DeeboMC: did he say wolfram seems better than langan?
Androzzo: clean member
Klingenwetzer: forsenWeird forsenWhat Didn't wash hands
StopitDonk: NotLikeThis dirty hands
jordangleanuk: SeemsGood NotLikeThis
jordangleanuk: NotLikeThis NotLikeThis NotLikeThis
bigie: does comma.ai use RL or do imitation learning from the driver data ?
st_gloom: you talk about washing hands you get banned
WearyBread: wash your hands u ditty pig
payrate: NotLikeThis hands bruh
Klingenwetzer: lmao how he smirked
StopitDonk: not 20 seconds
porteus: NotLikeThis
792x: handsfree 4Head
Klingenwetzer: HE IS EVEN HAPPY ABOUT IT LUL
jasonscottreval: Finally I logged in when geohot is live.
Klingenwetzer: you're beautiful george forsenHead
Jehhred: Soap doesn't exist in George's apartment
Bootstraps: yes
Krakatoa77: tbf keyboard/mouse would probably be worse than the toilet
lilou04: hell yeah
bojosos: go ahead
mashafique: rust? PogChamp
demonshalo: dont be rusty. he he he
l1ght5p33d: y
Bootstraps: that would be a good idea
luspr: Write it in coq
Klingenwetzer: @Krakatoa77 thats why I clean mine regulary
bigie: what would be the point though?
demonshalo: COBOL OR BUST
jasonscottreval: Rust hasan increasing amount of backers right now
Klingenwetzer: Code in C ResidentSleeper
Bootstraps: yes
badpartyhouse: no sleep[
jagger_rsw: EU waking up
payrate: We did it @chat
DeeboMC: @klingenwetzer is in for the coq 🙄
payrate: SeemsGood
StopitDonk: about friggin time PogChamp
badpartyhouse: wife is asleep already might as well just stay up
luspr: Handwasching stream PogChamp
Klingenwetzer: PogChamp DAD IS CLEAN PogChamp
l1ght5p33d: really what is good about rust is there some package?
covidneunzehn: its important, especially at this time! TriHard
Krakatoa77: It's learning PogChamp
bigie: you can't get corona from yourself. pee is sterile it's fine
Klingenwetzer: PogChamp CLEAN HANDS PogChamp SO COOL PogChamp I WISH I WOULD BE AS COOL PogChamp
b2kemann: let's write rust, i have missed those borrows and lifetimes
socialnotsocial: What were some of the best books you read in the last 10 years?
mashafique: Your stream is keeping me entertained as I play Oldschool Runescape LUL
aPosterior: close-up-video or didnt happen
Androzzo: Hi George, i'm from Italy!
jagger_rsw: I think he just ran the water but didn't use it to fool us :)
payrate: Everything is still in there @georgehotz o7
StopitDonk: PogChamp see kids, even chat wants you to wash your hands
Klingenwetzer: George is our neural net that learns from us PogChamp
semihchelik: 30 seconds
b2kemann: what about haskell?
Jehhred: Too late, you've already contaminated everything
Krakatoa77: with my limited context, learning rate too high is all i can guess?
DeeboMC: What about erlang?
covidneunzehn: "Superintelligent AI - 5%"
luspr: Yeah, but what is George's discount factor?
jasonscottreval: I don't speak from personal experience, but apparently it overcomes a lot of the problems with C++. And it sort of forces you to adhere by by its coding style. So most code is good quality. Can't say for sure though.
Klingenwetzer: BibleThump RIP GEORGE
Klingenwetzer: I will miss him
StopitDonk: why is it spaced out all over
Klingenwetzer: because python forsenK
bigie: ROS is still using python2. there's no way Rust replaces C++ in the next 10 years despite its advantages
StopitDonk: NotLikeThis
dostoy: more CTFs today??
Penguino138: @dostoy Nope TicTacToe and AI
Klingenwetzer: I wish I would be as cool as dad FeelsBadMan and wash my hands regularly :(
l1ght5p33d: so it's faster with defined classes
b2kemann: python, c++, javascript, they are all there to stay
DeeboMC: @georgehotz drop a mixtape banger called Dennis Ritchie
Klingenwetzer: I like how he touches his face all the time after coming from the toilet LUL
payrate: is there no Ctrl+F function in this "Jupyter" thingy, so you could search for -1 or somthing? I donno
zetleri: @Klingenwetzer you dont wash your hands?
Klingenwetzer: forsenS
Klingenwetzer: maybe
covidneunzehn: Yo, it's Geohot. still remember the time <3
bigie: so what's going wrong? value function/model/MCTS? i've missed a couple of streams
DeeboMC: Dennis > Lionel
Penguino138: Staying up l8
DeeboMC: Feels gr8 m8
Klingenwetzer: he is crazy forsenS
l1ght5p33d: let's make a new programming language with tensorflow operations
oldschoolfantastick: oeh
Krakatoa77: @georgehotz Maybe dome dirty variables in your notebook? Just try a kernel restart?
l1ght5p33d: new keras
payrate: @jagger_rsw gotta fill the coffee cup up, friendly reminder
Klingenwetzer: PogChamp
Klingenwetzer: 1 game
luspr: luspr is gifting 1 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 1 in the channel!
l1ght5p33d: * . *
luspr: luspr gifted a Tier 1 sub to l1ght5p33d!
Klingenwetzer: PogChamp
payrate: PogChamp
kayoeyumisaolegais: how long has he been streaming????
Klingenwetzer: Types in python lmao
Penguino138: @kayoeyumisaolegais !uptime
Penguino138: !uptime
Penguino138: nvm
jagger_rsw: @payrate tea person myself ;)
kayoeyumisaolegais: @Penguino138 yep
Klingenwetzer: 6:24h
Penguino138: Since 7:17PST
DeeboMC: @luspr nice.. now we can go subs only chat
payrate: @chat posture check!
kayoeyumisaolegais: @Penguino138 pt?
Klingenwetzer: forsenHobo
payrate: WutFace
Klingenwetzer: POSTURE forsenS 👉 forsenHobo
Penguino138: pacific time
Klingenwetzer: TAKE CARE CHAT!
payrate: NotLikeThis
luspr: @DeeboMC HeyGuys
movmap: georhotz how is corona virus programing project going? still working that idea?
aPosterior: it knows how to panic, great
bigie: shouldn't be a problem though. tic tac toe is pretty "shallow"
DeeboMC: @l1ght5p33d was 🔑; started from the bottom now my whole squad fuckin here
luspr: tic tac toe is more interesting than the virus.
covidneunzehn: pandemic solved @movmap
Klingenwetzer: Its called finding the global maximum is hard forsenK george
luspr: George needs a strong coffee
Klingenwetzer: yea like me
b2kemann: have you read a new kind of science @georgehotz ?
payrate: @luspr this
l1ght5p33d: instant coffe is best coffe
andrey18106: coronavirus will be with us for a long time
KyoshiDeath: Hello there
bojosos: Why would you want to limit the depth? It chooses what branch to explore using UCB
b2kemann: @l1ght5p33d enjoying some of that right now - hits the right spot
DeeboMC: @b2kemann my friend found that on the back of a toilet of rent house he moved into once
chowzor: it bothers me the spikes are getting larger
Klingenwetzer: HILL CLIMBING YAY
bojosos: can't the model learn all possible tic tac toe positions?
djceci: yup you can do it with a couple of ifs
DeeboMC: @b2kemann a new kind of science; not instant coffee lol
Klingenwetzer: ;-;
b2kemann: @DeeboMC looooool
BlackICEUK: BlackICEUK subscribed with Twitch Prime.
bigie: did you move the model to pytorch ?
midnightcookies: SeemsGood100
l1ght5p33d: stream 1337 af as usual
aPosterior: aka worse
Klingenwetzer: I got a leopold @jebivetar021 :)
Klingenwetzer: POSTURE CHECK forsenS 👉 forsenHobo POSTURE CHECK forsenS 👉 forsenHobo
payrate: @georgehotz take my energy DrinkPurple
DeeboMC: Tyra has left the building
payrate: HandsUp @Klingenwetzer
bigie: i notcied you pressed delete cell twice when you wanted to delete just one. I'm not sure if it was the training part though
gigafact: when are you moving out George? any timeline?
Krakatoa77: lets hope this fixes it lol
a_0__0_a: why do you looking yellow?
ImpalerV: it didnt fix it
ImpalerV: @a_0__0_a he probably has a screen warm night mode coloring app
ImpalerV: well OS X has that built in
payrate: come on @chat lets cling our smart heads together and help George!!!
Klingenwetzer: my monitor has that as well
a_0__0_a: oh!
DeeboMC: Last check point two hours ago 👀
Klingenwetzer: Okay I'mma throw random algo names in here
ImpalerV: @DeeboMC I always CTRL S, i guess he doesnt Kappa
Klingenwetzer: JPS
Klingenwetzer: Hill climb
Klingenwetzer: your mom forsenHead
ImpalerV: LUL
payrate: LOL
payrate: LUL LUL LUL
l1ght5p33d: happy hacking only
ImpalerV: chat trying to solve is could be like simulated annealing Kappa
ImpalerV: solve this*
Klingenwetzer: chat can solve everything
xmase123: !uptime
Klingenwetzer: even your spelling mistake PogChamp
ImpalerV: hey :\
Klingenwetzer: nymnOkay 👉 <3
payrate: what is the cumulative IQ of this @chat I wonder Kappa
bigie: tensorflow DansGame
ImpalerV: they were trolling me FeelsBadMan
Klingenwetzer: no he spelled something wrong @ImpalerV
bigie: no i just dont like tensorflow
ImpalerV: oh Kappa
l1ght5p33d: its an abbreviation
Sabre_of_Light: now you see what youve done.. theyre in their own world lol
covidneunzehn: chat = super AI
payrate: Kappa
lynchkin: what is MuZero?
ImpalerV: google has an answer Kappa
Klingenwetzer: chat is the best neural net humanity has to offer
bigie: reinforcement learning algorithm. i think from deep mind @lynchkin
lynchkin: ty
payrate: @lynchkin a quick search told me this: "MuZero presents a very powerful generalization to the algorithm that allows it to learn without a perfect simulator."
Klingenwetzer: -10 LUL
Myrmustin: destinys brother lol
covidneunzehn: twitch chat is always right
covidneunzehn: TwitchVotes
ImpalerV: we can beat SC2 but we can't beat TicTacToe Kappa
payrate: SeemsGood
DeeboMC: Prolly like ~400; I doubt it’s a multiple of the number of participants
l1ght5p33d: initial condiitions or rules
Klingenwetzer: can we though? @ImpalerV
ImpalerV: @Klingenwetzer i mean it is playing on the top ladder so... kinda. it competes against medium tier pro players at least
DeeboMC: ~400 iq projected
a_0__0_a: !uptime
l1ght5p33d: so general you can never lose
Klingenwetzer: not against serral on his own setup PunOko
ImpalerV: heh LUL
payrate: @georgehotz what can we do to help you?
ImpalerV: wntrSERRAL you mean Kappa
covidneunzehn: its not a bug. its a feature
Klingenwetzer: lamboGod
ImpalerV: LOL
Klingenwetzer: lamboGod kiwianPray
l1ght5p33d: geohot is the pinnacle of human intellect
b2kemann: learning is a hardcore drug man
ImpalerV: whats comma10k
Klingenwetzer: kiwianPray WE ARE HERE TO WORESHIP YOU @georgehotz kiwianPray
DeeboMC: @l1ght5p33d don’t be one of those guys lol
Klingenwetzer: *WORSHIP
b2kemann: read a new kind of science geo
ArosGeo: are you happy?
covidneunzehn: 2min Q&A PogChamp
b2kemann: you would love it
codelumberjack: how is small pharma going?
gigafact: next stream when?
Penguino138: You'll fix those bugs tomorrow. Thanks for the great stream
payrate: @georgehotz what is the meaning of life?
waynzcore: show feet!
Eclipshun: What do you think about Lex's new startup idea?
zetleri: Whats the 9th digit of Pi?
Klingenwetzer: Kreygasm
ImpalerV: LUL
Klingenwetzer: BIG PP
waynzcore: Kreygasm
djceci: you ever read the +orc cracking lessons
waynzcore: haha
payrate: Kreygasm
luvrub: thats a nice brand of dish soap u got there
socialnotsocial: Have you read Nassim Taleb? What do you think?
Jehhred: inb4 MuZero cures cancer
Klingenwetzer: JPS
covidneunzehn: instagram is dead. twitch game is on
Myrmustin: im doing a seminar about complex neural networks can you give me some guidelines foir my research ? ( its short ) ty lol
bigie: and we're gonna stop using tensorflow and shame people who do
bojosos: Did you like Th
Klingenwetzer: LUL
shr1ftyy: Have you read The Road to Reality?
l1ght5p33d: y
Klingenwetzer: D:
covidneunzehn: DansGame
Klingenwetzer: FeelsBadMan
bigie: probably not LUL
shr1ftyy: by Roger Penrose
Klingenwetzer: forsenHead
ImpalerV: LUL
ImpalerV: wntrKEK
DeeboMC: Because I figure you’re smart enough to know otherwise lol
Penguino138: its ya boiii penrose
covidneunzehn: he is 88
shr1ftyy: Yeah that one
Klingenwetzer: oooh that PogChamp
emel_ryan: PyTorch has been very good to me. Glad I started transitioning. It's the future
DeeboMC: Penrose is the goat
Penguino138: The Emporer's New Groove
ImpalerV: pytorch has been the future since like 3 years ago Kappa
bojosos: antiai SMOrc
DeeboMC: hes not anti ai
KyoshiDeath: the future is to abandon python for ai
Klingenwetzer: LMFAO
covidneunzehn: urgh
Hamudi069: what u up to
socialnotsocial: What were some of the best books you read in the last ~10 years?
fugebin: DansGame FBBlock MrDestructoid
shr1ftyy: what's ur opinion on that statement?
DeeboMC: he's anti ai = conciousness
Klingenwetzer: that couldn't stand up to anything
b2kemann: lol
sondreal: Remember to subscribe booiiis we all want more Geohot streams on twitch!!!
ImpalerV: hahahahaha
okeeeeeee: ??? LUL
GooberFN: @georgehotz THATS BECAUSE YOUR A P-ZOMBIE
ImpalerV: rekt
Ziv0: LUL
b2kemann: or coffee
Krakatoa77: LUL
covidneunzehn: acid LUL
Ziv0: or shrooms
payrate: Have you seen the movie Chappie?
SnadderG: Acid in a video game ofc
bigie: LUL i can't get my hands on any right now but sure i'll try
Binarylogin: woot acid
Binarylogin: of course
luvrub: thoughts on george hotz?
Thelazysinpe: Any good books for cs students?
Klingenwetzer: what if we all would drink bleach? Then there would be no wars and no corona virus that could spread PogChamp
bigie: have you read stepehen wolframs physics theory ?
inf42: whats the new game ur playing
b2kemann: https://www.wolframscience.com/
codelumberjack: we just saw consciousness
DeeboMC: not as smart as ai.... quantum based like humans
shr1ftyy: yes check it out!
oblomo: but maybe acid is only changing the consciousness
emel_ryan: anything you really miss during quarantine?
badpartyhouse: George Hotz 2024
shr1ftyy: have you read stepehen wolframs physics theory ?
b2kemann: we need a computational research project on twitch
mashafique: Soft voiced Geo quotes PogChamp
l1ght5p33d: humans live forever now
instagrab: you should work on a vaccine for cov19 = )
ImpalerV: anything you wanted to have accomplished by 30 that you haven't yet?
DeeboMC: or not "not as smart as humans?
Bassalisk: acid and DMT all the way man <3
a_0__0_a: how to get enlightened?
DeeboMC: humans"
ImpalerV: hahahahaha ok LUL
Klingenwetzer: general PogChamp \
Slybluedemon: Any good books for cs students?
payrate: LUL LUL
Klingenwetzer: well you are in the US forsenK
gigafact: what would you do if you got cancer?
Penguino138: Have you been to France? Paris is the best
sondreal: doesnt cs students have enough books to read these days LUL
ImpalerV: there's only 1 general in US Kappa
shr1ftyy: lol
b2kemann: this got dark quick
Klingenwetzer: cyber force of the US PogChamp
Jehhred: Always Remember, 'People will always let you down, except Rick Astley' ~ George 2020
covidneunzehn: elon will get you on mars sooner or later
DeeboMC: penrose knows what he's talking about; tegmark's the doofus
l1ght5p33d: HEROIN
byte_baron: machine learn your own cure
GooberFN: @georgehotz thoughts on death? what do you think happens after death? Are you scared of it mortality?
b2kemann: you sound like you have read a new kind of science
l1ght5p33d: for cancer only
payrate: what would be the next level of "Algorithm"? Is there another step?
covidneunzehn: :D
ImpalerV: gn gn
Klingenwetzer: lowVe
smurfd0: nite
Penguino138: Goodnight thanks george
sondreal: ELON MUSK
covidneunzehn: F @GooberFN
Hamudi069: gn8 dude
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: @georgehotz dont go PepeHands
luvrub: Streaming tomorrow?
Klingenwetzer: farming elon musk LUL
fugebin: gn george KonCha
SKPTCL: pce m8
ImpalerV: what did elon do?
b2kemann: paypal mafioso
lanop24: how hard is it to get a job at comma.ai
mashafique: Night Geo
sondreal: GN <3
l1ght5p33d: humera c1027h567
bigie: good night
Klingenwetzer: lowHi gn8 ma dude
DeeboMC: read michael talbot
covidneunzehn: jimpanseBye
shr1ftyy: gn
emel_ryan: good night
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: gn
GooberFN: @covidneunzehn How?
Klingenwetzer: hope you sleep well dad @georgehotz